hello and welcome to the junkyard love
[Music]
no I like to do self-improvement type
stuff I like to learn I like to shove
knowledge down my gullet and see if I
can understand some of it and I like to
share that with other people in the form
of recommendations at the beginning of
my podcasts so here you are today I'm
gonna recommend the rebirth of nature
that is on the Rupert Sheldrake YouTube
channel that came out a week ago I
listened to it on my way up to a hike
yesterday fricken made me totally it
made me think a lot when I was just
looking out at the craziness that is
nature it was awesome check it out the
rebirth of nature Rupert Sheldrake this
episode is with Mack T and J fall it's
awesome these are a couple of my buds
it's interesting to see the dynamic and
the just weird shifts that have happened
since then that was March 14th I think
was when we recorded it and the lock
down came into play in our area the 16th
it was a very quick flip switch so it's
interesting to listen to the vibes the
you know the differences in tonality
about certain things I think it's
something definitely worth pointing out
in taking a look at and kind of
listening to if you're listening to
anything that's old or new or just the
shifting vibes how they are day-to-day
and how our attitudes are so you know
transformed and instantly changed by the
news and scare tactics and what's real
and what's not [__] who the hell knows
what's real with this crazy news section
going on
do we can't take care of yourself be
aware of the changing times be as clean
as you can don't hang out with a ton of
people just pick a select for you keep
saying take care of your grandma let's
get going with the podcast cheers
friends when I jumped off and injured
myself
I jumped off the claim a breeze it
changed my life free like nineteen yeah
I can see it's recording so we're not
gonna not again it's not certain about a
good Jessica and Mackenzie I'm the two
wonderful friends
what's up welcome hi how are you both
today Jessica we'll start with you how
are you today I'm pretty good feeling
pretty hmm mildly inebriated at this
point you don't feel full of any virus
or anything yeah no I'm feeling okay I
got a little cough though so okay keep
it over there but kenzie how are you
doing we'll ask you to leave if she
coughs clearly I am great I'm happy to
be back home spending time with friends
and family it's been really good how
long are you grounded right now from
work yeah are you guys like cancelling
any flights anything like that yeah
flights I can't
we went down cut flights by 40% yeah so
and then we are grounding 300 planes but
I still have a schedule for the rest of
March so I'm gonna work that and then I
get my April schedule on Monday so we'll
see you think he's pretty drastically
then yeah they offered people leave of
absences without pay but I don't want to
do that so we're just gonna say hi to
pay rent and like I didn't think 12
years ahead of time of yeah and eat and
I didn't save any money recently so I
really need that but yeah I don't think
you're alone and then I think a lot of
us are the same way yeah so how are you
work like mentioned their 401k for he
was like you could take it I'm like man
we're here six months
do you think I have who 401k retirement
those are things that you know it's
scary to think about right now - I know
like they seem so insignificant at times
like these as far as like oh I have one
but that is it like that literally gets
me nowhere
well you got like 40 bucks sweet and
it's taxed so I mean I probably I have
one that I don't Jake I asked you how
you were I'm I am I'm doing pretty well
I I feel like a medium I my brain just
just goes to like I'm stressed about the
money thing because like cancelling a
lot of shows I played last night
but like got a text this morning like
hey you know there wasn't a huge turnout
so we're like we may not be doing DJ's
for the foreseeable future cuz like if
people are staying at home there's just
not a ton of people
I play soap star that's okay yeah and so
you know just like little gigs
cancelling and then like my spring tour
candy league's my big stuff cancelled -
for audio for audio directing so
stressed about that but I feel overall
fine like I think it's like obviously
Shea Lee's gonna work so we're not like
hurting for money but it's obviously I'm
taking a hit in the pride and that's
like you know yeah it sucks having to
like see her work and bust ass like
FrontlineSMS she's even a pardon like
the hard side you know she's a nurse
like it's it's if things get crazy it's
gonna be certainly crazy to her first
yeah yeah and she doesn't really have a
choice with everything going on right
he's like like she doesn't even Michigan
it's amazing yeah dude I don't even like
I'll try to tell her about like some
envelopment so there's like this thing
going on in Mike su we're gonna freak
out or they could what are we gonna do
like I'm just trying to see where we're
at in relationship and she's like yeah
that's that's gonna [__] happen to
him I says we're [__] game night yeah
dude she's just she's a leader like that
she steps into a role pretty well she
faces a lot of stuff without like any
hesitation yeah like if she has it you
don't see it yeah Shaylee we love you
she's gonna listen to this Shaylee Morin
she's gonna be listening to this
probably she'll be on her way home from
work so so be how many people do you
think this is sorry Shelley here we go
we've got to go on how many people do
you think listen cuz I know I listen to
all my stuff when I'm like driving to
and from work for the most part like how
many people do you think they listen to
your podcasts are doing it when they're
like in their car it got to be quite a
few yeah but I feel like people nowadays
do find time to like inch podcast like
at home like because some people will be
like I just wasn't three episodes of
your podcast in a row like damn you at
six hours we like well [__] I do that
with other kids [__] yeah yeah I I've
listened I listen to betos in my car but
the like the one with you too I listen
to it in the airport I had downtime
between a flight and I just listened to
it then I listen to my own in my hotel
room on a layover but I feel like when
I'm in my car I'm like jamming out yeah
I guess you're you're like in your car
is a lot different than like our daily
commute yeah so I'd say like yeah in the
airport between flights and stuff is
when I do it mostly but then when mine
came out I was on a layover so like any
listen to what I sound like is because
like you want to be so self-critical
like I feel like I get it with a lot of
people cuz a lot of people in the
podcast are just first time being on an
interview or talking or anything like I
don't have a ton of experience with it
either like we're always so nervous like
how did I say this two months or did I
did I whatever or did I say like too
much did I say um too much did I say so
too much me say oh that's interesting
too much that's what I say crazy that's
crazy
literally I was saying literally yeah
taking the word literally in our society
and they made it mean the opposite of
[Music]
97% of our odd lingo is like what how
did that get to that because that's not
what it means
yeah because we're like we're saying
things that what you mean I get the
feeling because language is us just
trying to communicate what feelings are
yeah and so what we're
with a lot of the stuff that our words
aren't exactly what they mean when you
say oh that's crazy I was telling you
guys it's not exactly saying well that
is crazy like that's that's a profoundly
textbook definition of crazy it's it's
I'm supporting what you're saying
because that was like wild and we're
still floating with that part of the
conversation yeah you know it's cool to
be like create like it's just support as
we're talking you know had conversations
well I definitely think we're harder on
ourselves like if I were to listen to
you two I wouldn't notice how many times
you say like I wouldn't notice these
things
I'd just be my best notice that's crazy
she literally texted Jake and Mackenzie
and was like you guys I want a podcast
with you I want to talk to you nothing
about it was like you guys said like to
my right and I heard you say this too
many times I feel like when it's
ourselves we're so we we're so hard on
ourselves on the time to do that is it
just a comparison thing like I don't
know probably it's just like I
socialized kind of conditioning where
you're like don't see this too much
because then you tell this way don't say
this too much you know well you know
actually obviously I'm certain think
about it with me I think a lot of its uh
we think that with the internet we think
that like we can be represented at once
like no matter how hard you try like you
can't be represented in like a one
podcast like so it's like how I have
McKenzie on it's like well now you know
everything about her like it's
impossible like so we're like we know
we're like so self-critical we're like
how great people are gonna think that
I'm a so-and-so because we're making the
correlation of like if I say like a lot
I'm some sort of like knucklehead you
know or whatever yeah or I think
everything's crazy any story cuz she's
gonna think it's crazy like yeah it's
crazy cuz and when I was listening to my
podcast I was like wow I think
everything's crazy every single thing
we're talking about I think sometimes
that's just our way of like containing
what we want to say like ya know how you
automatically are like okay I'm gonna
start saying something because your
brain is think not listening you're not
listening well enough so when you say
things like that you're like okay I'm
keeping on tasks with them
even if it's not really like relevant
you're keeping on task with their
conversation yeah I completely agree
with that maybe we yeah maybe we use it
like help ourselves focused yeah I have
to I think I have maybe I need a start
to the sentence before I start seeing
like what I really mean I just need to
throw something out there first and then
I go and then I continue with my thought
every sentence I'm going to say this
yeah it's it's cool though because when
you when you do hear yourself you know I
still do you kind of default back into
saying like in that sort of thing but
when I listen to myself and now that I'm
not so self-critical like I've edited
enough podcast and heard my voice so I'm
like twenty five thirty five times I
know and I'm like or you could edit it
out too
you know at the beginning I feel like I
did I would be talking to someone I
would lose my train of thought and I had
like so much shame behind that we had
that conversation in our podcast
yeah dude and I would like delete like
the outer like edit out that like three
second like where I'm like apologize I
can't
I'm so sorry like because that because
you think that you need to I own this
impressive host I'm this whatever is
like they don't [__] think that yeah
like oh they all listen to Joe Rogan hi
Tyler and I just said today like he says
he like gets in you're the face of the
person that's there and he'll say
something 17 times and like he doesn't
know you used to do all live
thank you it'll definitely in my podcast
with you I I think I was just like
staring at your wall and I totally lost
train of thought what I was saying and I
was like wait where was I going with
this
there's a lot to like grab your mind
yeah yeah this is actually grown quite a
bit since the last time that I think I
was here yeah I I've always had I once
since I started doing it I'd say once a
week i ride on it maybe once every two
weeks but lately I feel like it's like a
few times a day I've added like little
things that's great that means your
mind's working yeah I mean like that you
know
your brain is actually working God I'm
doing great so far nobody's here to see
it as like it's my brain you know
because there's so many whether it was
like all the things I listened to or
things that I read or lyrics that I
heard or other motivational people who
said it or poetry from me or whatever
like all these things are like just been
such my life the last like two
two-and-a-half years whatever and so
it's cool to see it's like oh yeah is
like what your brain has been doing so
it's a representation of well we talked
about that before I think you said the
phrase like welcome to my mind because
these are all thoughts that I've
collected Jay said that she came down
her Buckeye she's like wow it's pretty
crazy to be inside your mind or
something like that it definitely feels
like pot though I feel like that with
you night when I lived alone you know in
the old apartment oh yeah
did so much art in so much writing and I
go back to it now and I'm like who and
the heck was that person where is that
brain but I don't get that same kind of
alone time now I get alone time but it's
just not the same like complete solitude
and I think about it I'm like dang I had
quite the brain I have that same brain
but it's just I do a less of the like
invert type of like I would write it
down now I just I'm like what and poor
Tyler just has to hear it well now that
you know that you guys like do you have
more space and time are you going to try
and like dive into that side of your
brain again yeah absolutely I have like
a I'm excited for you guys to come see
it
I have Tyler has a room like a whole
room for his justice gaming in his time
because his alone time is his space like
he needs and he likes to play games and
I like to like create and read and draw
and I don't know like meld into this
creator I guess but I have a little den
that's like an art studio and like my
little library and my desk is there it's
technically my office yeah because it's
a business now
that's where our is yeah let's talk
about that yeah tell me about the
business yes we can
okay tell us certain things okay so
we're rolling out Lacy and I are rolling
out a little business we'll like mobile
bartending gloves yeah it's pretty cool
because it's something like and this is
something like Lacey and I want to do
together we want to do a podcast if
we're gonna do anything about it we're
gonna do something like Lacey and I cuz
you gotta hear from Lacey she's the
other half of this you know not so bad
good she's the [__] you're gonna really
like yeah you're gonna have you for
better I don't think I've met her but
I've heard a lot about I my little
Arizona gang is like Lacey from a z/os
series actually
hahaha well like everyone knows that Maz
mayor's on a friend yeah but we're
starting a little just like mobile
bartending it's technically like our
catering cuz we don't sell alcohol so we
don't have to like we get away with
things like we don't have to have a
liquor license we're just really
expensive and really costly and really
annoying and then where our goal is to
like eventually build into a company
that we can like leasing wants you know
like Brandon's doing wedding videography
and Lacey wants to be doing stuff in the
wedding industry or you know we don't
Lacey's a bartender she does want to do
that forever I never wanted to do that
forever so we're just trying to like
kind of do something that's like fun
like we can come to your wedding for
four to six hours and have a hell of a
time and we're fun yeah it's such a cool
idea yeah yeah I feel and it's so taboo
around here there's really not even even
like as much research as have we done as
we've done there's really not a lot of
mobile bartending companies there are
like our tenders who will come to your
event mmm like we have an actual bar we
intend on having a little like trailer
eventually that we can like you want us
to pop-up it the vancouver market okay
here we are yeah yeah so total your own
hours and stuff like that too you don't
have to make it this huge thing yeah so
it's it's a work in progress but it's
something that like Lacey's the creative
mind behind all of it and I'm just kind
of like that I know people like I like
an ocean yeah somebody to be able to
like I mean you could be a genius what
is like Steve Wozniak it's steeped
you know you need someone who's a genius
and knows the creative ideas and someone
who could present those to not look like
a crazy person to the investors yeah
absolutely I was like we're all planning
and Lacey's like here's 15 pages of all
these ideas that are like here here here
here here and I'm like Lacey we got to
work on one thing at a time and she's
like I can't I feel like I ring a bell
with that yeah yes that's awesome I'm so
happy for you guys do we start in that
I'll be like a new journey too and yeah
it was cool like we Thailand I took a
trip to Colorado to visit some friends
came back and like I got a new job a new
position I guess with ups different
hours which was super nice because I'd
the 4 a.m. thing was just a big suck
fest so I got a new position and then a
week later we had like put down on a
house that was a surprise that was
literally like Kyle and I were like
let's rent for another year and then the
next day we're like let's actually put
an offer on this buy this one yeah let's
do it and then then at the same time
Lacey and I were like let's start this
business like it just all was like let's
do it
life just hit like that yeah and I'm
like yeah and then you know as it's
coming up like oh my god but it feels
scary and amazing yeah it feels good
once at all levels out and you just get
organized it we are great we're moved in
now so that's like that's done that's
gone that's not even an issue anymore
yeah and the business is like pretty
much rolling and I mean right the new
house we have to wait that's why we're
waiting right this is like it the whole
world's on pause right now do you feel
like ye like you I don't know but like a
few years ago if this all this stuff
came at you would you feel as ready for
it and like do you feel like you've been
going through changes like improvement
absolutely I think um I never saw myself
which like I think you guys probably
both know this but like I always thought
I was gonna do service work social
services that was where I was going I
want to be the person who changes the
world and then I totally switched gears
a year ago
finished my master's degree in business
like that was super super outside of
what I ever thought I could do or wanted
to do and it's just things are just I
realize I'm presented with an
opportunity and I can either take it
because it's something that I'm like
that's a challenge and I can do that but
I don't think that a year or two years
ago I would have ever thought like hey
there's a challenge in front of me I'm
gonna I'm gonna learn that like I just
it's kind of off topic but not I just
applied and interviewed for a position
that's a full-time position at UPS and
they're like hey what do you know about
Excel and I'm like I know what I knew in
college you know I had to take it how to
learn it how to do it and then I forgot
it but I straight-up was like I'll learn
it like if this is a position that's
gonna advance like yeah it's oh nice I
literally said I'll watch YouTube for
like in it
hours so if you want me to but I never
would have said that and honestly my my
genuine self is like you don't want to
do you you don't want to do watch
YouTube you don't want to learn Excel
but like in my mind I'm like yeah you do
why wouldn't you I wouldn't want to
learn something new so I think I'm like
telling myself do that rather than like
straying away from it where the
encouraging voice is little louder you
know yeah excited you're doing big great
things yeah things he's like yes yes I
am you do you guys feel so a lot of the
stuff that I watched on YouTube a lot of
br-2 a lot of woowoo a lot of crazy a
lot about mother earth a lot about
nature so right now there's like
constantly talking about like the
feminine energy the the feminine energy
in the world it seems weird right but uh
I feel like the more stuff that I hear
and the more that you see like the last
few years of course we see it through
our lenses but I feel like there's more
and more people stepping into their into
their real selves like starting to just
like oh yeah I do want this thing better
for myself you know I'm like it's not
like all of a sudden we like are
magically millionaires or something like
that but
I don't know I think I still don't like
fully know all like the feminine energy
masculine energy stuff like how to like
properly explain it it's all it's a
little over my head still but uh I don't
know do you guys notice any like like
your friends as well as yourselves
because you both like we're just talking
about like going through changes like
feeling better did you guys notice any
other people in your lives any other
like women standing up and like feeling
more empowered changing this is a really
hard area for me is it I'm not trying to
get political at all by the way like I
don't it's not like a news thing at all
like oh no I don't know I think I'm
really and I don't know if this is like
for you but I think I've always been
pretty like strong female yeah I've
always had that kind of like I already
know what I need what I want what I have
I can change and I'm totally okay with
that but I feel like throwing the like
feminism and feminist and those terms
it's me riled and I don't know why I
don't know why it is but something about
it gets me like agitated yeah those
terms and that like oh right yes well so
so that's the annoying thing about the
media so when I'm talking about feminine
energy so if I had never watched the
news in my entire life I could be saying
exactly the question that has hands -
you asked you like like if you go
through like Buddhist texts and like
these things they talk about Fehmi
feminine and masculine energy so that's
what I'm talking yeah unfortunately I
wasn't able to like explain it as well
for asking a question but it sucks
because like the news media makes you
feel like like you need to like that's
crazy like that that like it makes me
bummed out actually yeah okay so you're
asking if any other women in our lives
have become more empowered is that what
you're asking or you just the
differences of it evolving like more
women empowerment throughout the years
or just differences between the two I I
guess my like corner of YouTube has been
talking about like the last like couple
years like the
of course there's on the media and stuff
there's like the feminist stuff and
that's not a nut not what I'm talking
about
okay just like say like a 35 year old
woman who has been living like in a
victim mentality and she's like not
doing good she like finally like like
leaves her abusive husband or something
like that like she finally feels like
all the sudden like more spiritually
inclined to like take care of herself
okay I'm I should I should be able to
explain feminine energy better but oh
I'm getting okay so that story kind of
helped me I'm getting yeah just let
you're saying I you can also say no I'm
just like no I totally believe that I
think with a lot of my relationships
myself even and people that I know over
it's weird that it's only been the last
couple years but if you look back to ten
years ago I felt like maybe it didn't
happen as much so I feel like that is
correct
I feel me myself I've really grown into
a person where before I felt like I let
people walk all over me a little bit or
I would make excuses for people treating
me certain ways and throughout the last
couple years I have been like no I need
to do it's better for myself like what's
good for me and not what makes them more
comfortable and so is that what kind of
what you're saying holy what I was okay
I was like am I just know I've
definitely noticed that within the last
couple years but it shouldn't just be
the last couple of years I mean this
should be I feel like I should have
owned up to these things and realize
these things years ago so I think it has
a lot to do with like our aging though
the process of like yeah becoming like
we're nearing 30 rather than 20 and I
think a lot of the things that we're
like seeing repetition in negative
things and we realized we're able to
recognize those now which is like a
pattern that you know you you remember
to brush your teeth as a child you don't
need me as as we get older we start
recognizing patterns that are negative
for us and then we positively are trying
to surround ourselves so you're just
like Luca part of it is just instinct
yeah instinct I completely agree with
that it's I feel like it's all through
maturing like definitely each year
you're grown
becoming more yourself and a better
person well hopefully becoming better
people and the availability of like
resources and knowledge and information
yeah drastically helped yeah he's like
you're right like 10 years ago probably
even though someone was turning 28 29 30
they may not have been seeing things the
way we're seeing them or as early yes
like a lot of I feel like a lot of women
were realizing things like in their 50s
after they've been divorced or their
kids were grown and gone yeah and like
we're like we're not even married were
not even there yet and we know what we
expect what we deserve and but same
thing for men like I think it's the same
thing for men where you're like okay I
can see that if I love this woman
genuinely and I put the effort into it
you know or it myself like men loving
themselves is far more common now than
it ever was yes even saying men loving
themselves would be like a weird
sentence yeah not that long ago yeah I
feel like more men are able to and
obviously what I see through like the
community I surround myself with as I
see like a lot more men in touch with
their emotions in touch with
vulnerability in touch with like their
own fears their own inadequacies like in
in so that those sides of us are like
those are like the feminine sides of men
like it like men have an equally
feminine side you know just you know
women have a masculine side of them as
well no but I think it's great I mean I
feel like men should be in touch with
themselves and what they're feeling they
should be be able to have they should be
able to be open about these things and
it kind of saddens me that that's not
normal because it should be normal for
both female and male to be open with
emotions and raw and vulnerable and it
sucks that just like recently now you
know over these years that people are
starting to open up with it more it
makes me sad that before people felt
like they couldn't right yeah it's
like as like the counselor homie of my
friend group like a wide range of people
like for many years I get like not doing
so good man like those sort of texts
like really low and like these guys like
you can't get that far with them a lot
of the times you know like I've always
been a pretty emotional dude I grew up
with three older sisters you know so I
don't know I feel like the it feels like
as a guy a lot of the times you can't
really get in touch with your emotions
like you you understand that they're
there you can make I'm not doing so good
and then like when it comes to like well
you got to look at them and you got to
inspect them and you got to say like hey
man what what is that emotion mean
they're like I am NOT doing that that's
that's girl [__] like you're you know
what I mean yeah like they'll back up
and so I think just or it's a space of
uncomfortability right right so that
like incompetence in understanding your
emotions leads you to like ignore it or
avoid it or put it off or just it'll go
away cuz I'm a man and that's how we
deal with [__] right yeah your boss well
yeah I feel the problem is gonna keep
persisting unless you dissect it and
figure out the root of the issue and
what's going on and it does suck that a
lot of men and women too it's not just
men but a lot of people will be like
nope
like I don't want to face what's going
on so I'm just gonna put on a brave face
but it's all about figuring out what's
wrong because once you do figure that
out it might hurt but you're gonna grow
from it and you'll be able to face
things better I feel like in the future
right I think the same to say for women
I know that as because like I was saying
I've always been a very strong female I
know that sometimes I don't have enough
humility or ability to humble myself and
say like wow I feel pretty unaware of
how to do that a lot of for a long time
and I would say the last few years I've
been really good about like just saying
like I don't know how to do that but I
feel like women have had a long stretch
of like we've been like driving or
selves to be this confident and this is
I think partially just social media yes
the kind of like the bid war are you
this or this or you this like I'm not
sweet and sultry and I'm not gonna post
daisies and flowers on my but kind of
want to cuz they're cute yeah sometimes
I'm like [__] I want to post like I'm
all dressed out in black and I feel you
know I have like 15 different personas I
want to be but I never will not I
shouldn't say I never will I used to
never like humble myself enough to say
like I actually know how to be soft and
sweet
I actually know how to like I oughta
flirt weird enough and I'm like funny as
hell you know they're like I wouldn't at
the time I wouldn't humble myself enough
to say it so I think it's the same for
women where you like maybe I have the
man's mindset like you grew up with
sisters I grew up with all men right hi
maybe I grew up in that like don't let
other people see your insecurities or
your whatever but like a lot of females
now I feel like don't want others to see
their insecurities until recently I
suppose recently I suppose yeah I feel
yeah growing up like we're like you were
just saying if I didn't know something
or I would be embarrassed almost I did
oh I'm supposed to know this or
something about Africa yeah like I don't
want to ask questions or like okay I
need to go home and not really
mmediately now I'm like I'm human I'm
not gonna know I'm not gonna know like
everything that all my friends know so I
feel I'm more comfortable now to be like
hey like what is that yeah like I'm more
comfortable with being embarrassing well
speaking of your whole life from
McKenzie we didn't want to loop back
around of that bridge story I did okay
let's get there it is okay wait this was
an actual injury like this was the
things I I do I do see that this an
actual injury it's silly I just want to
say like as I'm making fun of it
please also know that I care about you
be here when I tell like the injury
aspect of it it's like the surgery and
stuff it's even hard to believe like me
sing and like this [__] doesn't happen
to people and then I'm like nope of
course they happen to me like okay so
where do I start
okay so it was a summer day two people
who don't have bridges to jump up and
the wind was okay no it was the summer
before my senior year and we weren't
drinking like I know it's hard to
believe the way we were also very well I
made this is horrible to say it was like
a background though like what what is it
about our town in our area like there
this is very common yeah this cherry on
the side well I feel like our hometown
was literally just going down each
sentence well okay yes background our
hometown doesn't have a lot of
activities to do when you're younger I
feel weren't drinking them or drinking
No
so one of the things we would do is jump
off this bridge and it was pretty normal
I feel like in the summers absolutely I
feel like you heard story oh yeah we
went to claim a river we jumped off the
bridge maybe that was just my friend all
right it's interesting to think like if
there's people from Florida they
probably what the [__] are you talking
about like we live we joke with
cliffsides we jump off of like all these
things into these really cool rivers and
lake areas
yeah like when I was hanging out with
this awful human he said we did gainers
off the off the tool like bridge and I
follow you sorry
like I remember saying I'm thinking like
oh that's normal
yeah I know not one part of my brain was
like yeah it was totally we yeah we'd
have a group texting okay let's meet up
here
I mean go swimming yeah that summer I
was at the group of 10 people and we we
were up the river more and we were cliff
jumping and I jumped off the cliffs
everything was fine and so then we go
down the river and we stopped at the
bridge and everyone's jumping off of it
and I remember I wasn't gonna do it this
is where peer pressure comes in I would
never do it now if I didn't want to but
I felt absolutely oh yeah that was in
high school you know everyone else was
doing it that sounds so stupid saying it
no it's real though for that time yeah
when I was that young everyone's like
just do it Mack and I was really
hesitant at first and then everyone kept
jumping off of it multiple times and in
my head I'm like well no one's I'm just
being a baby like no one is getting hurt
and so yeah I did it and it's 70 feet
I believe the bridge it's really really
tall and I jumped off and I was in a
pencil dive because everyone's making
sure that your feet are crossed so I was
like okay and then I jumped off and I
remember the fall being so long that you
have time to like think out thought
processes like that's how long it is so
I remember falling and I was like damn
I'm like when am I gonna hit like you
have time to think about it
and when I'm gonna feel when I hit the
water my body had curled up into a
cannonball in my ass yeah I hit the
water and I instantly knew something was
wrong before I even came up and so I
like reach the surface and I couldn't
swim and so like I was in pain like
don't laugh now I was in shock I was in
a lot of pain
I knew something was wrong and Stephen
minke was there and I was kind of
yelling like help like I need someone to
swim me to shore and I remember I think
goes him he jumped off when he jumped
off he was fine he swam to me and I
remember we had to climb up this
hillside
and I'm just like I was like something's
wrong like I need to go home now and my
ass was bleeding and god this is
embarrassing okay so then I went home
and called the doctor and they said this
is completely normal you just tore your
rectum and the other they said it was
common not normal what was your like
what at this point I I think I was in
shock like I just remember hurting I was
hurt and I didn't really quite know what
was going on and then I remember
thinking I remember telling my dad and
he did not feel sorry for me cuz he was
like if you're [__] friends jump off
a bridge would you it is like he's like
it's a sing Mackenzie and you're he's
like you're that dumbass so I'm liking
all this pain and my dad is just like
you're so [__] stupid and I was like
well now I look back I'm like well yeah
he had a point as a parent though you've
got to think what is happening what have
I done
he's like what even hanging out with
your friends and you guys just all
decided to jump off bridges like as a
parent yeah they're probably like well
anyway so I didn't have surgery then but
years later when I was living in
Bellingham my tailbone just turned black
and blue like all the way up my spine
and I was having a hard time sleeping on
my back and like right where like my
butt crack starts I mean it started
hurting so bad so I went into the
hospital I went to the hospital and they
did an ultrasound on my ass
you know an ultrasound of all things and
up my spine and of course they don't
know the bridge story and they came in
they're like you have had trauma severe
trauma to your tailbone is there can you
name a time like what happened you like
yeah they said that it was complete like
to this day my tailbone so cracked like
it never broke it's still fractured and
they're like what could have done like
Nate what could have done this and I was
like tell us and so I told I told them
and they kind of laughed but they also
on the ultrasound found assists had
built up inside of me and it was from
the water in the river that shot at me
into my body it stayed in my system and
all the bacteria and the river created
assists and so I had to have surgery on
that and get it taken out I kind of
remember that part that's so wild and
yeah and it was years later which was
the weird thing like it - it was like
over the years like yeah all that
bacteria had stayed it was just so gross
had stayed in my body and built that but
I I mean it's funny to laugh about now
but why not if it was traumatic but when
I came back to school I was really
pissed off because it was my senior year
it's how everyone's gonna remember you
and I was like okay I was like okay like
only a couple people know like it's fine
as I remember you know how you used to
have to before school started you'd have
to come in and sign up for classes no ok
well at Kelso before I would have to
like go in the week before school or
something oh you neat with your advice
you have they're like yeah you got your
schedule before school even started well
I went in there and there are a couple
guys in there and they just started
laughing right when I walked in and I
was like they're not laughing at me
whatever and then they're like hey Mac
like we heard about your ass in the
bridge and I just remember I was like oh
my god like school hasn't even started
yet and when I came back my senior year
that's how everyone knew me and everyone
wrote to me in my yearbook and like
called me Mac torn
and said oh that's we're back torn and
they were like Oh miss your ruptured
butthole and it was just all yeah it was
all about the bridge and I was so
embarrassed but as the years have gone
by it's funny because people bring it up
and I laugh about it it's just like dumb
[__] you did it's like that story it's
like if someone told me I be like yeah
right that didn't happen like that's
dumb that would happen to some of them
and it's like nope me like if it was if
it was another party body like if you
broke your arm they wouldn't beg how you
broke your arm like just because you're
but we think it's like as high schoolers
we think like with us make whatever okay
but like how old are we no we're still
laughing yeah I like saw someone last
year from high school and I think they
were like wait you're that girl you're
that girl that tore ass and I'm like
cool later years later it's still there
there's other things about me social
media at that point oh you should be
thankful that there was a very mild
social media then that was probably was
it was Facebook even yeah yeah it had
just started cuz right only graduated
towards the end people were getting
Facebook and I got one right when you
graduate yeah but yet MySpace we did but
I don't feel like I used my face as much
I used it more when I was like a
freshman and a sophomore in June and
then like I had it kind of like how I
have a Facebook now but I don't really
use it it's the same it was like the
same and then Facebook came along
literally like right when we were
graduating and yeah I felt I honestly my
senior year I feel like I didn't use
myspace so much yeah maybe yeah I was
still laying on train tracks with my
half black half red hair upward camera
with eyeliner I use that I tried to I
had tried to find him a while back go I
tried to like search my old myspace
profile I think I had cool pictures you
did no you were cool like I wanted to be
your friend like I just I loved you own
like me and Gunnar and like Taylor and
stuff we would go out into the woods
we'd go out to the train tracks would go
like find a ban and bill
when we were like 16 15 taking pictures
yeah like weed I remember I bought this
you know what maybe gunner and I split
it he wore one glove and I want the
other girl is skeleton glove and like
you take the photo of like like your
hand reading kind of see like the glove
in the photo this is hilarious but like
back then I feel like it was like we're
still just like we're teenagers who just
discovered the Internet like the
internet was so cool and just anything
you did and post on the internet was
cool and just like cameras really to
like think about like actual cameras not
even your phone cam yeah like gray do
you member the razor phone camera yes we
were [__] they were so they were really
good yeah I feel like I took a lot more
pictures with like a legitimate digital
camera oh yeah those were I had the
digital a red one yeah I didn't have any
of those Britney Jennings did and she
was like the queen of pictures yeah I
don't see isn't that I don't know that's
weird I was like good friends with Brit
for a pretty long time and then like I
didn't know I never knew you guys never
knew anything about it because I was
like anti a Kelso I was when she was
Britney - and then you mentioned Taylor
yeah the people though here yeah it's
not weird
for those of you don't know those are
two people that passed away yep missing
piece just to them yes we all have
drinks yeah listen untouched glass
because you guys have chrome eyes
stays on plastic or 3ds so it is
interesting to think of I love like
explaining about and just like thinking
about our town area because like yes
we're a small town likes like Kelso
Longview like cats rocks definitely a
small town I'd say but like Kelso in
Longview is like a like the mega part of
a bunch of small towns like it's like
when you go into town and you live the
cows walk you go to Longview right yeah
anything
yeah like it like Longview Cal says kind
of making town but like I talk about a
lot like my like you know like kind of
foolish lens on life in high school like
I would affiliate the whole town of
Castle Rock where I live now with
hillbillies yeah like Old Country and it
was just because the way that I saw the
world was like rednecks beat me up and I
know they live in Castle Rock so I like
was afraid of it was like didn't like
them and it's so weird how like
our [__] view of an entire place with
the world or wherever could be and we're
like this is true I viewed Kelso as you
guys had a daycare in your school so you
were all [__]
honestly like me now it's like hell yeah
more power to those girls who made some
pretty crappy decisions with those guys
who made pretty crappy decisions and
they had kids a little too early but
like you're still going to school yeah
me then was like wow you love flat nope
yeah cuz my little virgin ass yeah it's
definitely all about maturing oh my gosh
our thought process is when we were in
high school man I don't even want to
well I thought I was gonna be married
and have kids and live in the town of
cast rock at age 23 like I was like I'm
gonna have kids and this is my perfect
life and like I genuinely believed that
because I didn't know anything else like
I didn't know any 23 was my age - that's
funny I was like when I'm 23 I'm gonna
I'm gonna be married I'm gonna have my
first kid because I don't want to be it
like an older mom yeah I'm gonna be a
young mom I'm like I'm like I was pretty
drunk in Arizona a lot yeah living in
Arizona barely paying rent barely doing
a whole lot of anything and I'm like
yeah how could I have forced a child out
and then raised it to not be like yeah a
first glass of wine in a while well it's
weird that what I was more concerned
with was being an older mom like that
when I was younger I was like I don't
want to look old when I have kids like I
want to go to like their graduation and
look good that was my thought process
playing a child into the world
like how can I raise this kid nice hair
nice meals think like that though in
weird ways you know we forget what's
important sometimes I kind of want to do
I don't want to get to there until I
have this figured out yeah weird I think
about it now and I think like even age
30 seems like I'm trying to have a kid
in a couple years
yeah I'm scared I don't know like it's a
shame that I've been talking about it
and it's like hit like we'll have
conversations like she was just in here
before this and she's like a [__] kid
then like you know last week we're like
daydreaming like like trying to figure
out where we want to be with it and the
future is around that like it's so funny
go to school all the time or like we
can't have a third dog no we can't don't
you have room for the dog no no we don't
have room for the dog we just got a
king-size bed for the first time and
we've been dating almost three years and
we've had to hug the whole time and
Grandma Thatcher's still I tell them
they're still sleeping on the outsides
of the bed like here's put your paw down
no we're thinking about getting a dog
well we're still thinking about getting
a dog it's definitely gonna happen I'm
very excited a goldendoodle
I feel like I want to be in my head I'm
gonna be the most like savage dog dude
like I I'm just like stroking my ego and
it has even happened yet I'm just like
gonna be the coolest dog you're like
thinking about getting all the toys and
taking him running all the time yeah and
I feel like I'm in like train him and
like learn like German commands so he's
just like the smartest golden whoever -
I don't know maybe I won't but sounds
fun you have to teach him American
though oh my can english-american raffle
is this how other like other people here
ask normally at your little you know
like when you're having a function in
the backyard
someone will be like sit and your lay
down and your dogs like I don't listen
to that I listen up flats you know oh
yeah oh that yeah only commands and I
feel like dog names I want to strong-arm
Shaylee with that really bad I just want
to be the one who names a dog okay so do
you have any names in mind up a huge
list my boy or girl is very dependent
also so we're gonna go for boy yeah yeah
male dogs are just see I'm biased I just
feel like like I had it what if you
would if you accidentally call your girl
dog good boy you know she didn't like
what the [__] goodness boy and they're
like I'm a [__] girl yeah I have a
lot of names picked out I like I like
weird names though like I don't like
like spot in my ex Duke like I don't
know I just like typical dog names like
ever like when I had a hedgehog the
amount of people that like is his name
Hedgehog there is air his name sonic I'm
like well no me
that's pretty traditional I don't know
what that's most like stuck-up thing to
like even care about but I don't know
I've been thinking about a lot of names
too I just watched a movie and this
dog's name was meatball and I really
appreciate it because it was a big
burner
Brittney's Mountain dog it was just
people like you at the park and if you
yell that go party McKenzie do you think
you ever gonna have an animal I don't
know it's my job well so one day in the
far future when I get married um if he's
home enough then yes I would like a dog
I won't want a cat and I wouldn't want
more than one dog like if I'm gonna have
a pet I feel like I'd have one um just a
bit of advice though two dogs play with
each other come on just one that's more
aggressive than the other one does
exactly he does yeah more aggressive
about attention to you yeah yeah so it's
just
I'm gone a lot with my job so I feel
like another person would definitely
have to be there yeah help take care but
you do like dogs I do like dogs you
could just get one now and have Gabby
and Danielle take care how would they
work night shift - so they're not there
half the time well they should take it
they should take a little time off work
could do puppy daycare - like I know a
lot of people who have pretty it like
long days and they take their dogs to
puppy daycare it's expensive it's a that
sounds like money it is I'm like baby
are you gonna be home who's gonna let
them out there's a there's a puppy
daycare it's like a I think they're an
exit up but grandis who is the Great
Dane dog next door here he goes like a
couple times a week on to this like
short bus that they painted like with
dogs and stuff comes and picks him up
and they literally pick up dogs like
school bus stop and take him to like
daycare for the day and then they drop
them off later and it dude it's like the
most delightful thing to see pull up
next door the cool you get a cup of
coffee and wait by the window his name
is Granderson he's just like this big
giant Great Dane of course you need like
anything he does is cute of course but
yeah crying time for the mobile bar
after it's going for it years ago
wow that is just like the bit most
beautiful picture that I just you just
painting me thank you
imagine if you're in traffic and that
pulls up next to you turn my car off
good I would not be okay to drive what
is it about dogs but well where did I
kind of wanted that that'd be cool thing
to learn like the origin of dogs and
cats like when do we start and why did
we start like it wasn't just like was it
like there was some Wolf's that were
like more chill and we're like does that
want to like do you want it and then
you're like asking your friends do you
have a feeling inside of you that we
should put our hand on that you know
like the merchants
and a dog would be like usually they're
afraid of like Wolf's and [__] but I
really know how it happened did we like
breed a bunch of like new breeds of dogs
cuz they look way different I have no
idea I always imagined that like it was
like a slow evolution I'm just like you
know how you you can be in the same
space as somebody and you're like you're
chill we don't have to talk I like you
from over there or like we've agreed to
disagree or agree to just share the
space without like any speaking that's
how I feel like you are with a dog and
then if I'm slowly evolved to like they
just take over your whole [__] space
feel like you know whatever kind of
evolution you believe in it started with
like they were kind of the like how
animals in the traditional ecosystem
decide if they're either enemies or
they're okay with living in the same you
know in the savanna is a good example
there's a lot of animals who live
together fine and then there's you know
these [__] lions come in whatever
like I imagine that that's how dogs and
humans and cats and humans kind of just
evolved as like we're chill if you just
like let us like ourselves here on this
place for some reason past I feel like
cats don't belong in that I feel like I
could see that for dogs but cats I just
like that they're up to something like
they're like still trying to trick us I
was gonna ask you I was like what do you
think it is like everyone loves dogs and
then there's like there's a percentage
that love cats I'm not necessary that
people really love cats
yeah mysteries though I feel like dogs
are favored more and it's cuz you think
that cats all right creepy or they're up
to something I think dogs are more
submissive and so I think that's why we
as humans are like right yeah you're
right cuz I know when I come home I get
this weird little pride of like my dog
is chewed on something he shouldn't and
he's hiding in the corner and I don't
eat my dog but like he knows he did
wrong and he knows I'm in charge yeah
who knows when I walk in the door he's
it and I get that little like aha you
know you know what you do it like you
come in if your cats [__] up your
house and you're like the cats just like
you just looking at character in
tomorrow like yeah no I'll take a [__]
on your carpet okay he's like I'm
[__] as I'm looking
now in the I don't like not not every
cat is like that no but I feel like more
often you get a lot of that is the cat
like the cat I don't know world you have
to just be okay with like never knowing
or never like they don't you can't be
like hey come here spot
let's go potty the cats like don't do it
okay I like doing that yeah they just
don't listen as well I think I like I
like personally the submissiveness
without I mean that's you know what for
me to say they're just now nobody's
really probably - though that's probably
a lot of us yeah why we like animals
well I think I don't even know why but I
like dogs butters I just like even like
in personable I think too than cats cats
are very like standoffish and even if
they're a lovey cat they still are like
I'll have my space for 14 hours and I'll
touch you for 30 minutes dogs are like
can I be here all the time
I just thought because we just got a new
dog out my dad so when you're saying
that I was like thinking that in my head
like picturing our new dog yeah did you
do you have animals growing up like dogs
and cats going out yeah so the reason
I'm not like super attached to animals
why wasn't a lot of my friends and
family would make jokes and say like you
hate animals they'd always make fun of
me but it was because my parents got
divorced when I was two and I felt like
it was a competition between my mom and
dad so when I got a dog on one side the
other parent was like oh no I'm gonna
get her a dog too so I got two dogs but
they both died and yeah at my mom's old
were you when they did I was pretty
young I don't remember I was like one
was an elementary one was in middle
school it was tragic I'm sure yeah
because I grew really close to them and
then my neighbor actually shot my dog at
my mom's side because my dog Riley loved
porcupines I don't [__] know why but
oh is like if it saw it was hunt for a
porcupine and attack it and then I come
back to the house with quills
all the time well it chased a porcupine
in my neighbor's yard and my neighbor
shot it
and drop the dog okay
yeah he was just an [__] and so
Reilly was still alive but it hit like a
main artery and he wasn't gonna survive
so he had to basically just put him down
but yeah so growing up after my dog died
I just decided not to get attached to
animals cuz I think growing it just was
traumatic for me growing up I was so sad
I was at a young age I feel like I would
handle it better now but I was like nope
I don't want to be around like I would
pet him but I just wouldn't get very
close with any animals we even got we
got more dogs and stuff I just kind of
kept my distance because growing up I
was like well they're gonna die at some
point so I don't want to get crazy we
learned that from like such young age
but like oh this is what happens yeah
because I totally invested myself in
those animals and then so I was like
nope I'm not gonna get close and so it
was like a joke in my family like Mac
hates animals like don't come in here
like it would say that way I'm like I
don't hate animals and they're like
you're just not a very affection I'm
like because I don't want to get close I
know they're they're gonna die and so
now I feel like I'm more attached like
we just got a new puppy and I've been
over there and all my time is just we
fell asleep on the couch last night
together it was like Raptor on my leg
yeah it was so cute so now I'm getting
like more attached but it's been years
since I've been this way so yeah I
honestly don't think that I loved dogs
as much until I became friends of
Shaylee really yeah like I I definitely
loved I've always loved dogs we've
always had a dog but we've had outdoor
dogs so I've never had the same
relationship and then I met Schiele and
she was just like loved dogs and then I
slowly like and then I got an indoor dog
and I had my own dog and it was like
life-changing so yeah dude it's actually
crazy i i recently so this was just
probably a month ago actually it was
with Shane and I were talking to my mom
and I asked my mom it was a real memory
because I thought it was a had like a
traumatic memory about dogs and I
thought that it wasn't real
but I confirmed it with my mom and I
when I was younger if like when my dad
was doing drugs I was messing with we
had a pit bull dog a pit bull puppy I
was messing with him when he was
sleeping and and he like woke up because
I'm a kid messing with him when he's
asleep and he bit me any I guess it drew
blood around my eye like it didn't know
my actual eyeball but just like the skin
around and yeah and so he bit me and
obviously I'm sure I was crying like I
was younger in my dad like on drugs he
like react and he grabbed the dog and
took him the woods and shot him like
like and so and it was crazy like
talking about this with my mom because I
realized like Oh like I like put my own
fault in that because as a kid through
that lens I'm like I got it killed yeah
I just yeah and it's crazy like stuff
like that you know in a it's like I just
emphasized what you were saying cuz like
we hold on to these things like we put
like almost like like I don't want to do
that I'm not gonna bring that love to
him because I don't want it to be
destroyed it's a weird thing yeah yeah
dude it's crazy but I think that like I
love dogs now and I have like
progressively more and more the longer
everyday Shailene are together you know
like Julie is a dog lover and now like I
feel like and then we had Bentley here
we had Megan's dog here for for quite a
while and like I love that dog so much
like I feel like it's a whole that I
didn't realize I had but it's definitely
been filled in for sure yeah
but it was like it was interesting to
like hear that story of moms like yeah
that happened it's so weird how we like
how we both like held on to stories like
that right and yeah yeah and I because I
would never try not to pet dog you know
it wasn't an intentional thing I was
just like nope in my own space and
finally I came to the conclusion I'm
like you were like that's why I like I
don't want to get close that's
consciously like yeah why do I do this
every time I've done this so many times
where I say unconsciously a lot of you
can kind of apply it like awake
conscious is a consciously consciousness
all of that it's like such a broad used
word yeah like it's I read this book I
think it's conscious or consciousness
can't even remember now by Annika
but it's like Anna Faris yeah Annika
Harris so I was like I probably just
wanted to tell you guys that I read that
book is it a good read books I don't
read them but from Qasr try I read them
books I read them books do you read do
you read so much yeah yeah what's a
recent book that you read um actually I
have two books that are in my like oh
I've been reading Harry Potter's though
I decided to reread Harry Potter not
read them oh you did no I did yeah
actually I stopped reading I think the
fifth book maybe and then I never
actually read the other ones so I'm
starting from the beginning I love here
I will watch those movies on repeat I
have a good problem we don't own those
anymore but like I know what they are
like exactly I know number four is my
absolute favorite
absolute favorite I think that was like
my favorite book scene I don't know cuz
I don't remember the books as well cuz I
read them I was always a like in first
grade I was reading like a fourth grade
level
I always loved to read and so I've
always read above but I used to read
format a are points I never read for
pleasure because I was faster as me to
take the test to excel at school but I
never read as like a pleasure thing so
now I do it in like recreation but I
have two books that my my girlfriend's
mine Arizona friends they all like pass
around books and so we've I guess we all
do oh no no worries
yeah it's awesome it was like it can be
like really girly books or like there's
a book called educated by I think it's
Tara west over I think that's her name
I'm like picturing that I've heard that
thought books so good yeah I haven't
read it yet but I have like I've heard
my little arsenal of books to read you
know what it's about enough to like
describe I don't really I know it I
think it's about like her like growing
up I'm pretty sure it's just kind of
like a memoir it's about I don't know
exactly what's about that everyone says
it's about her overcoming a lot of stuff
like she was in a really bad place and
then gets to this really amazing place
and the
journey that she talks about is just
really good but I personally haven't
read it either but a lot of my friends
have read it and then I was in a
bookstore in the airport just kind of
browsing around and this guy came up to
this random guy was like read this book
and that's what the book that was
sitting there you're like and I was like
okay I'm gonna read it he's like no
seriously it'll change your life
so dude I always loved following ID like
I always I always say those like
intuitive moments like okay I have to
[__] read it yeah I don't know who
that guy is but yeah why would you tell
me to read that book he's a shaman
honestly you meet some coolest people in
the airport and some not cool people
yeah we're there periodically enough to
meet cool people and she's like I meet
all of them no there are a lot of great
people through the job and then just
people on the plane some people are
really nice and you'll strike up a
conversation there's a lot of yeah like
I said not the best on the plane as well
but no I feel like I've had really good
experiences like as much as I despise a
layover I've had so many of them that
I've gotten you know like I've been able
to like go sit at the bar and talk to
somebody that I'm like I would never
have been like hey wanna chat yeah you
know like get me on my plane get me home
but I feel like I've been put in
positions where I've had to like just
hang out and chat and not like deal with
it at the time I'm like damn I'll just
deal with talking to this guy but like
now I look back and I'm like oh that was
pretty cool conversation like yeah I've
had stuff like that to where I'm in the
airport it's I was at a bar usually and
most sometimes a bookstore I guess but
I'll be sitting there and you meet
especially New York when I'd be there
you just meet every like people just
came over from Europe and they're
everywhere or they're flying to New York
to go overseas you meet all types of
people so I've had some really good
conversations at the bar do you remember
anything in particular like like I met
this fantastic guy or anything like that
was not that
no I'd have a magical moment no actually
Jacob and Dimitri had just passed away
and I was having a really hard time
dealing with it and so of course I was
at a bar in the airport but I was
drinking a beer and I was sitting there
and there's a couple next to me and
they're from Ireland and they just
started talking to me and they expressed
me that they had just came there for a
funeral and they were having the hardest
time dealing with this death and they
had no idea like what I was going
through they just they opened up way
before I did and I remember sitting
there and we had this really good
conversation and just about healing and
things like that and it was a older
couple they were probably in their 60s
but it was just a great conversation and
it was that reminder like I'm not the
only one going through this yeah like at
a time like that you're so consumed in
your head and you're so depressed and
you don't know how to find a way out and
talking that I felt not that they were
sent to me about I feel like that was
supposed to happen because it was just
one of those moments where we talked for
like an hour and it just made me feel
better
you've been talking about it because I
probably would have sat there and just
been like another one and not like you
know just drowning my feelings but yeah
it was just a conversation about healing
and things like that and so that is the
one of the big moments that sticks out
meeting so awesome yeah and I've always
remember that was serving what was that
like where you talked you like found
people that you were just like wow I'm
so cool they got to be my customers
today like I'm so glad I got to chat
with them and got to know this about
them like it depends on the flight so if
it's an hour flight and you have like
200 people to serve I'm usually not
talkative I'm kind of I just asked all
three people like hey what do you want
you know and give them snacks but if
it's a longer flight and someone's
striking up a conversation with me I
feel it's hard the boundaries are hard
because on the plane some people don't
want to be talked to you know some
people are in their seat it's kind of
hard to learn that because if you try to
talk to someone they're like I just want
my drink put their headphones back in
and they don't even take it yeah I don't
talk to me and then some people I'm like
hey do you want anything and they won't
take their headphones out they look at
me and they're they just shake their
head and like they won't acknowledge
like they'll just keep watching my movie
so it's hard to find that boundary of
like hey should I strike up a
conversation because there's been times
I'm like oh hi I think I've tried to say
something and it just goes nowhere like
they're just like I'm watching like
James Bond like leave me alone
yeah watch Daniel Craig anyway but no
I've had a lot of great conversations
with people on the plane and also going
back to like people being sad there's
been people that are just bawling in
their seat and I'm like hey what's wrong
whether it's I'm scared of flying or
there's a lot of feeling like people
travel to go to funerals I've dealt lets
out a lot yeah and just like trying to
help someone during that time like some
people want to be left alone but some
people start to open up about it right
away and so even the littlest gesture
like do you want to drink like drink on
me like what do you want and I'll grab
them something and they're like thank
you so much so just navigating that
there's not a lot I can offer on the
plane but usually honestly even some of
its just the contact of another human
someone who like looks you in the eye in
character you know you really don't know
what people are going through and I try
to keep that like as annoying as people
can be believe me like when someone's
being rude to me of course your initial
thing is like I'm annoyed like why are
they being rude but then I have to think
maybe this person's like scared to death
of flying granted they shouldn't be
being rude over it but still you know
there's different reaction though that
don't realize they're doing yeah that I
try to just consider like maybe they're
going through something I used to take
everything so personally when I first
started yeah like I would do it you
being in New York especially people just
look you up and down they say rude
comments and I took everything to heart
but over the last four years I'm like I
can't take it personally like I didn't
do anything to them that's just them
having a bad day so I kind of just yeah
I kinda just brush it off now but I'm
rubber you're glue everything you say
bounces off me and sticks back to you
don't edit that out
halfway through I was like am I
remembering this if I [__] this up have
you had anything pop up for you like
what like you've worked with the public
in tons of different ways like anything
pop up for you where you like we're just
a little more human to someone in it
like opened up or they were like a
little more human to you and so you
talked about like deep feelings with a
stranger it's kind of connected with
them anything like that I mean I can
talk to literally anyone I have a I have
a like almost obnoxious knack to just
talk and say me that's true I know that
you I think that you are you're good at
seeing people's needs and like meeting
them where they're at like you're good
conversationalist with yeah being able
to relate to many different types of
people so they feel more open with you
if that's what I see yeah I just I know
myself and I know I talk a lot but I
think for me it works I think it's a
super super high like not a lot of
people can do that so you're right it is
something that was like it doesn't come
natural to everyone Tyler for example is
a great example of someone who cannot
talk to everyone or me even he has
struggles to talk to me I definitely
feel like as of lately um
where I work is to a very like it's a
fine line it's in its ups for anyone who
doesn't know that and I'm a manager so I
am not a union member and if you've ever
worked in a union or against in Union
because that's essentially how UPS is
set up I don't think it's intentional I
think it's essentially was supposed to
like be a cohesive little unit but it is
really challenging to work with someone
and say to them I am instructing you to
do this it sounds absurd and so superior
and so just like you both know it's just
farce weird thing I can't do it and I
actually like this is something I've had
a struggle with cuz I'm the friend
leader if I'm gonna be your supervisor
or your manager I'm gonna do it on the
same level as you yes I can do your job
but I'll also help you do your job and
I'll
you know like yeah I don't know so I've
had a root that's been it really
actually been a challenge for me but I
found myself being able to like lately
in the last just couple of years maybe
three to four years I should say um
reflect and like understand that this
drunk person at the bar or this [__]
driver he had a really bad day the
person who loaded his truck sucked at it
so there was his whole day was just kind
of backward and off and his routine was
messed up and so he probably is coming
in here and he's pissed that at 7:30 at
night and I'm telling him he has to go
help somebody else you know like you
just worked at ten and a half 11 hour
day and I'm also telling you like you're
at the bottom of the food chain buddy so
you got to go work another two hours and
then you got to come back tomorrow in
twelve hours and do it again it's hard
it is hard and and to be so I've been
able to just be your friend and say like
hey can you please just do this for me
and tomorrow I'll get you you don't need
me and so I think I've learned it I
think through the years I've learned
like I wouldn't want to do that but I
also know that I would go above and
beyond for someone who I trusted or or
respected or vice versa
so if I know that my supervisor is gonna
she is gonna follow through tomorrow and
like I'm gonna work an eight-hour day
instead of a 14-hour day or she is gonna
like let me event and be drunk and be
obnoxious and then tomorrow when I come
in I'm gonna apologize and she's gonna
be like no big deal you know like I
think I have learned to be a little more
human in the aspect of like give and
take yeah it's hard to be in a manager
position like that especially like
having to manage people you become
friends with yeah like sorry like I'm
your boss like you have to do this but I
love you you know what I mean yeah it is
hard it is hard to you know even like um
substituting has been kind of a
challenge for him because I go in with
this like I have to be an authority
figure because that's how the school
structure is designed but then I also
I'm like these kids are like dying of
insecurity you know and I'm like I don't
want like these girls will talk to me
and they're they'll be so [__] to me
in the middle of class because they
don't want to be embarrassed because
they were they were trying to be funny
or they were trying to be cute or
whatever and I'm like don't do that and
then I go back to it and I'm like at the
end of class like I
well little JIT like I think you were in
that group chat and I like legitimately
was just flat-out apologize to the
students for you know like I'm sorry
that this is how your class went but
this is how I felt blah blah blah blah
you know and like even that is hard as
someone who is 10 20 years older than
some of these kids right it's just being
vulnerable and just saying like hey I
know that you had a hard day but like I
had our day 2 and we're on like an even
playing field now dude I think a lot of
a lot of where that comes like where you
get success with that it's like kind of
snapping people out of it like without
like being rude and without like trying
to attack exactly like whatever they
just said because a lot of times
whatever the crap is they're like
yelling at you were saying to you it's
like not really what's going on they're
just they're having a bad day or they're
bummed about something at home or
whatever they're just kind of like using
this situation as defense against
whatever they can do but I think that
like having the ability to kind of like
not not call them out but kind of like
be like hey you know take a look at what
you're doing right now yeah you don't
want to be doing that like I had a I had
my buddy who's a paraeducator Eric he
was over here yesterday the day before
and he was talking about isn't he no or
anything so long a school district okay
yeah but uh but he forget exactly what
he says but he works with like some some
younger kids and sometimes he'll he'll
be able to kind of pull them to the side
or kind of like look down them I came in
you want to be doing that do you yeah
like or you know it's some sort of like
something he says to them like one
little sentence that kind of reminds
them you know and with kids of course
it's it's easier but sometimes with
adults I feel like we need in this is a
perfect example but just freshman mind
last night when I was DJing I had this
woman who she was just drinking having a
good night you know but she was like
when she'd come to request a song she'd
get like aggressive if I didn't tell her
exactly what she wanted to get request
no but but I actually like I was I don't
know I just felt super calm and she was
having a good time she didn't mean harm
she was too drunk by the end and I was
playing literally the last of two songs
two more songs and she was coming up to
basically just drunk staring at me
she could think of a song name and yell
that like she was like she didn't know
what song request she was just doing the
song request thing yeah like waiting for
a song to pop up and uh telling you know
whatever and then she just like started
like Escalade inch like yeah you're not
playing my request and like all these
things are starting to get mean and then
my buddy Kelly is also a DJ was up there
and she's like started like trying to
like be mean to him finger in his face
like it just like escalated into this
thing and I just like stopped her and I
was like listen seems like you're just
having a problem with being told no
right now yeah and that's that's a very
like strange thing to say it's like a
grown person yeah but when when
someone's drunk and you don't want I'm
not like trying to usher over security
to get her like kicked out that's not
but she what she wasn't leaving it was
like how to deal so I was like listen
you're just having a problem being told
no I promise you it's nothing against
you it's not personal I'm just not going
to play your song that's that we're done
we're done with that and then what
happened like what meats saying you're
having a problem being told no kind of
like pulled out of it because her next
thing she'd like waited a few like 10
seconds and started talking to me about
she's like what my son plays music he
likes music she switched to this thing
yeah like so you know she's just drunk
but but essentially she like me saying
that like I wasn't being rude I was like
listen I'm sorry like I can't like
you're having a problem being told no
Stern with that but I was like your
songs not being played that's that it's
done yeah I like making her realize that
she's arguing against like thin air
there I don't know I just kind of pulled
it out of it and then she started being
like a regular human again she's like I
have a son and he likes music and
there's music in front of me you know
yeah yeah so that's a drunk person
example but I feel like with with young
kids with adults like sometimes they
just need to beg hey man you're you know
I've been there too I get upset too like
you're just frustrated like I'm so sorry
it's been a long day like if I can help
you out tomorrow like you said like I
got you tomorrow like but just just be
aware of it like if like you can pull
people out of it like a lot of times
just like hey it's okay that you're
feeling what you're feeling like just be
aware of it yeah here's when I'm at work
I can't react the way I want to which is
a good thing because if I could say what
I wanted to say on the plane
it would not be good so serving teaches
you that huh working customer service
makes you like yes yeah yeah bite your
tongue it's crazy how intense I'm able
to say things like like imagine if you
said that to a person you're so I know
yeah I think it probably right email
about me if I said that but there's a
lot of times I've gotten yelled at how I
know it's not me it's just you made me
check my bag and they start screaming at
me or there's no overhead bin space like
what do you want me to do it like it's
not my fault you know playing the Pro
Pack one thing yeah I got it I got
screamed at because someone didn't get
the seat that they wanted and I just
looked at him I'm like you booked your
ticket like did I booked your ticket
right right like it's and then they're
kind of like well and I'm like yeah so
this isn't my problem that you're not in
not see like I have no control over the
seating like this is something that you
could have picked like you could have
picked the seat you wanted but you
didn't and so they kind of just like you
kind of check them like that but I can't
I can't say a lot no I think that's
that's great right right there because
people think they can say whatever they
want and sometimes like hey like I
understand that you're mad but you're
being rude to me and I'm a human
remember yeah like that's enough to like
remind reminding people like oh I also
make mistakes in any subtlety is enough
I think for most people some people are
just gonna be like oh now you're mocking
me now you're condescending now you know
whatever but like I think you can work
your way out of it in a nice enough way
saying like oh my gosh I'm so sorry like
I did not mean to make that mistake as
soon as you use the word mistake I'm
sorry I made a mistake or like I'm sorry
I'm human you know like without being
condescending because that sounds like
dickish but you can talk mostly
everybody out of their like anger I know
if someone were to say like I'm sorry
I'm human you know I would be like oh my
god I'm so sorry I'm even mad you know
like even totally take me out of that
headspace someone called me a
[__] you were like oh yeah I
went excuse me and he goes I'm so sorry
was over a seat though I'm like why you
gotta call me a [__]
well we're a [__] airplane seat it's
just [__] like that I'm like are you
kidding me you gotta bring the thing we
talked about the podcast like you're
about to be in a chair in a metal thing
in the sky sit down yes I mean I know
it's my profession in technology you
tell everyone this it's so great so
crazy but sometimes I I'm in the air
this might make me sound stupid but I'm
like how are there thousands of pounds
of cargo all these people all the fuel
and we're able to fly in the sky like
I'm just thinking about like how are we
flying like I know how but so I'm like
how is this it's such a weird College
the videos that show the thing
underneath the wings like how the air
goes underneath it but you're like okay
that makes sense but you're like still
doesn't [__] make sense when you
actually think about it it's insane and
I'm use actually crazy yes I think about
that all the time people like well
you're a flight attendant and I might I
don't care like it's still weird that
we're able to just be 35,000 feet up
with all these pant like so much weight
on the plane and we're just like
floating in the sky and it's crazy but
yeah but we would talked about another
podcast people will be like oh the Wi-Fi
hasn't worked in five minutes
and I just I'm looking at them like
you're sitting in the sky like you're
not even supposed to have Wi-Fi yes
you're not even supposed to have half
the [__] we have on the plane
yeah and accommodated to an insane
insane extent for people to just have
comfort right what's our like cap here
like at what point are we gonna be like
I had to move my left pinky that get my
drink yeah yeah no people are like that
sometimes in first class oh you didn't
set that right in front of me yeah like
on wall-e where they're just like never
seen that movie I've never seen that
movie either title two plans we gotta
watch it Wally
it's a great really good I've never seen
up either and I haven't
either what we've got it or something
that really is crazy
yes I've never fully watched The Lion
King you didn't like so you didn't see
the ending what did you do that kid I
watched Jurassic Park on repo yeah but
I've never seen I've never sat down last
year it was it was playing on the plane
like the animated version not the new
one I was like hey I'm finally gonna
watch it and I fell asleep I've never
seen anybody missed the bump though I
feel like it's like it's not like it's
like a crazy and throwing movie as we
have so many crazy baller-ass movies
it's just I think the timing wise like
dude's know why it was like the first
color movie I think you know I don't
know that I've ever watched like a lot
of the like ya princess movies all the
way through I think that it was around
at the time like cuz I I didn't grow up
I I think that I had like seen a couple
of them but I didn't really grow up
watching a ton of Disney movies either
yeah but my interest in them now is like
I've seen Lion King now
but mate Rossum announced because they
like compared a lot of it to like
philosophy and stuff so when I was
little if I like something I stuck to it
and I never tried a lot of other things
so if I watch like I watched Fern Gully
and did you ever see that yeah I was
obsessed with it I would watch it and
then I'd rewind it and watch it again
and so I felt like the couple movies
that I watch like my parents like why
don't you just put this and I was like
no that's not like but I do that still
like I I used to watch The Notebook
[__] depressing in college and I just
can't picture you liking it that much
you ask any of my butt like ask Liz she
poor girl she's live with me but I would
come home from from LCC and I would have
like three hours between like practice
in school and I would lay down and I
would watch the notebook and then I
would wake up and go to practice
but like my friend Meghan would come
over and she she like will tag me and
things like oh the notebook is here and
I'm like oh my god Alice in Wonderland I
did that to like the Johnny Depp version
of Alice in Wonderland I watched I still
probably if I had a DVD player I would
watch it on repeat wait so I want to go
back to the note
why do you like it like what were you
searching the notebook is a great movie
but to watch it every day like what were
you searching for was a just watching
their love story I'm a hopeless romantic
and at the time I was in a relationship
with douchebag yes in a relationship
yeah so I was watching for the I I do
this with all of those movies like even
now like Thailand I was relationship is
great but like romance and like that
that like drawn out that that is my like
creative side is very like emotional and
deep and romantic and just like full of
feelings and I watch things like that
because that's a way to get that out
okay but like in my real life if Tyler
were to come home and like write me love
letters and do this I would be like I
would feel uncomfortable if it was
actually happening to me in my life like
that's why Thailand I work so well
because he doesn't do this like cheesy
corny [__] like he's like hey babe I
bought my own protein bars this week and
I'm like thank god you're not gonna eat
mine that's romantic but I just turned
me but like if you were to like I don't
know I just think I don't actually like
the whole concept of it I like the idea
and the background and the depth and
severity of they like I don't actually I
don't think I actually am a hopeless
romantic I don't really want you to
light candles cuz I'm like those look I
like those ones and I don't want you to
light them unless I'm ready to you know
I'm like I don't really want a bath cuz
it's gonna get cold in five minutes like
I'll make my own bath okay I don't know
I'm just like I think conceptually I
like it but like realistically I don't
okay that makes like a nice little
fantasy to live there yeah yes that's my
fantasy yeah cuz I was like are you
watching this cuz you want to cry like
why you watching everything it's the
depth and the emotion and like that cuz
there is a lot of an emotion and yeah I
think that whole movie can be solved by
just a little more communication right
but it's also you know if she would have
broken up with her husband first so do
you this is this was an interesting
conversation with me my mom and Jay Lee
the other day when
watching a movie like I realized that
like people with different like thought
processes in ways of seeing the world
actually like see movies completely
different of course but like so as I'm
watching a movie I'm every character in
the movie like I'm projecting myself
into like so when they're crying about
their whatever like I'm thinking of some
sort of similar yeah it's a similar
motion that I can get to there and like
matching it like so like when I cry
during an emotional movie it's because
I'm like riding the wave of this actors
right so like I'm like putting myself
into the movie like I was talking with
Shaylee and and she was I was telling
her that and she was like yeah I just
like watch the movie she like seiza
objectively informed yeah like it like
in [__] but she cries nonetheless like
she'll you know she's emotionally she's
invested as well but she doesn't
actually watch movies in the same way
that I do
she cries from the story you cry as the
human or as the character yeah like I I
cry from like an understanding like I do
whatever I can to throw myself into the
understanding of every single character
in that movie like that's what I'm doing
and watching me but it's what what do
you do what about you Mac do you Canada
it depends on the movie I feel like some
movie Jurassic Park like Jurassic Park
[Laughter]
movies like Jurassic Park I just love
this I don't put myself in the
characters like the storyline fascinates
me just like the whole DNA aspect of it
and just like the bet not even like the
t-rex II okay I'm getting carried away
but anyway I just watch drastic but
certain emotional movies I don't put
myself in every character I would say
but it does go through my mind like this
this way that this character's feeling
right now I've gone through that and I
can like relate it to times in my life
like when it's like this hopeless
romantic like not good scene or whatever
and someone's sad it's like oh I like I
know how that characters felt like I've
been there and so that makes me
emotional but sometimes it's a storyline
to like I know it's fake and I'm like I
want them to work so
and it's like max they're not together
every hallmark movie I watch them in a
mic they're gonna fall in love and it's
like the same six people downtown yeah I
was like did Mac I know that you've
liked One Tree Hill The OC like I was
thinking about it so like there is one
character we always like did you do OC
and One Tree Hill no I did One Tree Hill
was my [__] man there's like one
character that you saw The OC for
example Ryan who's like the like poor
kid trying to fit in with a rich kid
sort of thing like I remember he's so
mean like I was like I was like just
understood everything he was going
through like you like think you're
living this little secret life through
him you know yeah it's like I totally
get you yeah yeah I felt like I would I
wasn't like
Marissa but I was in a way just the way
she I I don't know I wasn't exactly like
her like her character but I could tell
like how she hid things and tried to
deal with things like she'd act out in
certain ways cuz she was feeling all
these emotions but she couldn't get him
out just punch the mic sorry but she
couldn't get him out and so she would
drink or she'd do different things and
it's like I've definitely coped with
things the wrong way and so I get where
she was coming from I her character is
very dramatic but then I could see
behind that like she's gone going
through all this [__] at home and with
her her past relationship so she's just
trying to cope and she's acting out in
these ways so what we are what character
you on One Tree Hill
I don't know right skills think of all
the characters now I know what about you
Jessica what's here on One Tree Hill how
long has it been since you watched it a
long time since I moved back to Arizona
that's what Brandon Cruz like it when
Brandon Lacey started dating Brandon met
me and like I was just stoned on the
couch watching One Tree Hill they would
go through a stage meets me and I'm like
potatoes on the couch I'm in like six
hours later him and Lacey come
still I didn't have a job when I first
moved back like it was just like I'm
going back to Arizona I have 600 dollars
in my pocket like here I go
and then I'm just like smoking all their
weed and laying on their couch this is
your friend you talked so good about
like it took me a week and he's like
does she do anything this cannot be one
of your best friends like I don't
believe you're Lacey and you have this
best friend hey sometimes you need that
time to just sit on the couch and get
high represent you like you're who you
are your whole life honestly that was a
good like that was a good solid time for
me because I don't take breaks yeah like
I do take my take some naps and I do
chill but like I'm always going and
there's always [__] going on my brain
and like I'm always planning and going
and prepping and making sure this is
done in this is done in this done and
that was a time where I was just like
I'm gonna exist I'm gonna exist and I'm
gonna take a break and I'm gonna let
myself just decide where I'm going I
feel like you were pretty happy when you
were when you were like going to Arizona
my [__] yeah oh and I kind of know
exactly what's what I'm supposed to be
doing but this feels right right it was
just fun like it was literally just pure
like I didn't have to it like I was
going to college but I didn't have to
have a career at that point my best
friends were my roommates and we didn't
have to like make a bunch of friends
we'd have to work that hard like it was
just I mean we worked a lot like we all
were servers so we all were working four
and five days a week eight hours 10
hours 12 hours but it was just like fun
it was just fun my life do you go ahead
Mac no you go like so Shay then I notice
I guess not just servers but like just
thinking of like when we were young like
we were once like the 17 through you
know 22 year old or 16 through whatever
like we were the ones working the
customer service like we were behind me
and Shay like we were selling people
stuff with PacSun and clothing stores
and you working in coffee shops and
serving and because you were customer
service yeah we were yeah for like 60 so
do you
I don't know I always just try to like
and I'm not saying like this is a hum
percent or anything but I feel like I
noticed less engagement from the person
on the other side like so when we go to
packs on like the the person working I
kind of feel like an old man like all
these kids don't appreciate what the
habits or something like they aren't
engaged they don't like they're not like
hey how are you like they'll say what
they're told to say yeah I know but they
don't like actually like really talk
like a lot of times it'll be like
they're texting behind the counter or
whatever which is you know big deal but
I I don't know do you guys think I guess
just compared to your time working
serving have you noticed any change like
you at a younger age versus kids now at
that same age what difference is I think
a lot like you're saying the texting and
said there's a lot more social media now
and so I feel a lot of relationships are
over the phone like I I do believe
people obviously still talk in person
and meet up in person but a lot of
dating a lot of different things are
behind the screen and people are
attached to their phone so I feel that
customer service not all of them but I
do see the interactions in person are
just going way way down because everyone
is so used to communicating over like
with their phone now and back their
skills yeah back then I feel what we had
Facebook like all this stuff wasn't
really it was up and coming but I'm
thinking back to like my first job I
didn't have an Instagram or anything
like that I was way more personable at
that time when I was 16 and stuff I
think I had a myspace yeah that was it
and then but of course like as I grew up
and I was still serving when I had
Instagram and things like that but
definitely I think the more those more
the social media world has grown I can
notice people aren't talking as much
face-to-face that's so interesting like
to think of like like we're sharpening
our skills in so many ways like there's
so much good and so much knowledge
through our phones and stuff but like
they do you know it does take away
another areas like we we do lose people
skills and people skills aren't just
like so you can get a good job and you
could do good at interviews like people
skills make you feel
when you're able to like have an open
conversation you know with with your
shoulders back and actually like engaged
within conversation with a stranger for
example like that's a that makes you
feel a certain way you know like like
when you're able to like be open and
have even with somebody that you like
like one of your friends like you know
if you're not able to have like the same
friendship as you are through the phone
in person it's different you like we
literally feel different when we're
engaging with people yeah in
communication so I wonder if we're just
like maybe losing a little bit of that
like just as a byproduct of all the cool
things that our phones are bringing us I
definitely feel like I engage and have
always engaged with older people mmm
like in college when we would go to away
games like I have a pretty vivid memory
we were like at like a buffet or
something and I'm standing in line and
my whole team is there there's like 20
of us that are 19 18 and there's like
like a older couple that's standing in
front of us and they like turn around
and make the conversation and I'm making
the conversation and that everybody else
behind me is just like avoidant and it
to me I'm like oh that's normal because
I am so used to talking to people that
I'm like oh whatever but the net now I
was like older and I reflect on it I
know that I talked to a lot more a lot
more older people will talk to me and
have the conversations and I don't know
if it's maybe I just give off a presence
that or I have an open body language or
something that says like I'm willing to
speak to you but like if I go to the
grocery store the old lady ahead of me
is gonna make a joke about something I
haven't and I'm like oh haha you know
and I play into it but like same thing
goes I see it with Tyler he gives off
this like don't talk to me I don't
really wanna have a conversation with
you and I don't even know if it's just
cuz he's like I took completely
different personality or what but I know
that when we go places that I think I
just give off a like talk to me I'd love
to have a conversation you know I like
hi and sometimes I go and I'm like oh I
don't talk to people but like I still
get talked to you because I think a part
of just my something in my body language
says like I'll chat even if I don't want
to I'm gonna chat
and I think a lot of a lot of people now
and a lot of kids especially like I go
into places and I'm like I don't want to
talk I'm not gonna even strike up a
conversation or make a like funny joke
or nothing because they're they're just
doing their thing I think it's just I
think it's body language
yeah it's peculiar because I like when I
was incredibly depressed I feel like I
would like try to give off the vibe of
like hopefully nobody talks to me
hopefully nobody talks to me like you
you wear your hat a little bit lower you
I mean when it comes out I'm huge on
like physiology and like like having
your shoulders back pushing your chest
out for me like helps so much with with
like confidence and stuff I feel like
for so long our just the we're like it's
baggy closes I could and now we're just
kind of be hunched over and like if I
got a hood I'm up with that on to those
sort of things but uh and like people
people do pick up on that you know like
they don't and it's not like you're
walking around like with it with a
scythe and you're like you're like the
dead floating group or anything but
there is it it's kind of interesting to
point out you know there is like a vibe
just by like your body language your
posture like what you're looking around
at of like I'll talk to you or I'll be
nice to you or whatever and I think that
it compounds I think that it adds up
like my my anxiety when I go into a
store like instead of thinking
constantly like hopefully nobody talks
to me hopefully nobody talks to me and
you're kind of thinking about yourself
because you're anxious now now it's like
I'm just walking around the store doing
my thing like I'm shopping you know just
I'm not everybody else and I just know
and I just trust that if someone does
talk to me I don't have to have it
planned yeah I can just talk to them and
whatever I say is okay like I I feel
like I'm just using a grocery store I
guess for that example but I don't know
I think I'm just kind of curious like I
just think I like to think about things
in the long term like you know kids who
are six years old and in there like
gonna have the next 20 years of just
technology and they're not really gonna
be learning like these outward like
human like you know if there's nobody in
your life that you mimic that has that
and you don't have like the ability or
knowledge to like do it yourself then I
don't know because because you can make
your depression worse and you can make
you
make yourself feel worse by punching
over and not being open and all these
things I like learning from others my
dad was always a chatty person like we
would go places and he would talk to
anyone and everyone and I think that's
probably why by nature I feel that same
which is super bizarre I don't know I
don't know why I like mine it's a it's
for me it that's a like male/female
thing females tend to talk more but my
dad has always such a Chatty Cathy like
we go to the store and I'm like oh
here's 14 people my dad knows what he's
talking about on average when you're a
little kid just looking up at your dad
like what's he talking about he's I mean
he's probably like reconnecting with
like how you been you know he sees
somebody from high school and he chats
with autumn or he talks about like Oh
work or you know I mean I don't know if
he anything my dad is the goofiest guy
so when I I think maybe I've just seen
that my like we'll walk out of the store
and my dad will make it a point to go to
that girl scout and buy those cookies
because he wants to make sure that
they're supported and you know and it's
like it's things like that I have never
recognized until now I'm an adult and
I'm like oh like I Tyler this little
girl said would you like to buy some
Girl Scout cookies and he like avoided
her and I was like no I was like you
don't even say anything you said I
smiled like that does it I granted is it
huh I was like offended by his reaction
like we're nice people like I think as I
grew up on that like yeah it's probably
being around your dad and him being that
way that's how you grew up and you're
you talk a lot not in a bad way
but you know you notice you're like oh
and I could I can joke and you're saying
these things about your dad and it's
probably you grew up that way and so I
think life is all about human connection
I mean honestly everyone wants that
human connection but you're talking
about like this generation of kids if
they're just on their phone and they're
not say their parents are at work and
they're not having a lot of human
interaction they're just gonna they're
gonna have social skills they're not
gonna know how to connect with people
because everything's based off
technology in the phone right well and
their parents they go to the restaurant
their parents give him the phone to keep
him quiet you know out of their hair
and so then they're just by nature like
every time they go out to a restaurant
that's what they want to do is be on
their phone rather than have a
conversation with the person next to
them I think it's very common like I you
see that in between people walking in
the malls people walking in any anywhere
you see so many people you see all these
groups of friends going out and they're
on their phone
I mean weed I definitely am guilty of it
I'm always on my phone but I'm also very
aware of my connection to the people I'm
with yeah so I can yeah I feel like both
I feel like I used to I used to be on my
phone so much more but it's because I
was just like just super depressive and
like I wanted to be like I was just
self-conscious and like thinking like
you just get caught in your own brain
but now like when I'm like oh I'm on my
phone or like I'll check something or
like you you know give yourself a few
seconds on your phone and then then now
I have this thing where I notice I'm
like oh yeah you're on your phone and
you're actually at Applebee's with your
friends remember you love your friends
like yeah and in like just like that
like quick little reminder nothing
arguing in your head but all that just
hit that lock button on the side of your
phone and turn it face down and just
look at one of your friends and say
something you know I mean my god like
it's seriously weird but like it helps
like and none your friends are gonna
think you're weird and just like I feel
like it's a weird thing to point out but
we almost have to this phone this thing
is so great that we almost have to like
oh yeah there's so much there's such
thing as too much of a good thing like
this is a good thing too I'm not gonna
miss this thing that I'm reading on
reddit or this like Instagram you can
read it later yeah but like I'm going to
like when life is over or in six years
when I'm reminiscing about what school
in my life this is gonna be one of those
moments yeah and and if you're not
careful you're just like spending those
moments on your phone you know so I
don't know that's where I've changed I
definitely I make it an effort and I and
I you know even if I'm feel a little bit
socially anxious socially anxious or I
just smoked a big joint right before
super nervous [__] man it's okay to be
high your friends don't care and then
I'll put my phone down and I'll just
talk to him about zombies or whatever
you know it's like we've all been
friends for so long like even outside of
this room all of our friends know we're
weird
everyone everyone my first and
yeah no it's just when I say [__]
they're like yeah that's just you well
dude I mean none of us know what we're
gonna say like I don't know what to say
my god I never do none of us like we're
just talking like in and when you have
friends around when you have people that
just love you no matter what you know
like that it's just like you have that
trust here and I feel I got so many
people have that but we forget about it
sometimes and we get heads and we just
want to be on her phone and and safe you
know I get on my phone it like at night
when I want to Pinterest and I'm just
kind of like trying to be mindless cuz I
just want to like go out kind of how my
day was and I do that as like a way to
kind of like it's almost like a mindless
thing for me so if I'm looking through
Instagram it's likely because I'm just
like looking to look I'm not really like
come I've stopped after I did that like
three months almost four month I think
um I took like a I stopped comparing and
now I'm just like enjoying like oh my
friends are doing this but I'm also like
my friends are doing this and I'm just
kind of like using it as a means to
digress a little bit from my day we
don't think you complicated yeah which
for me is like that's initially what it
should have been poor but I start I got
too involved in it now I can look at it
objectively yeah yeah I appreciate that
now cuz I didn't I didn't want to delete
social media like a couple months ago I
was like I don't really want to delete
it I just want to like use it as my in
the right way and now I'm using it as a
like sleep mechanism that's not as
reddit I used to read it before bed but
I've read it for me is like yeah it can
be like your internet sort of so it's
like my interest so I have like a bunch
of like audio stuff and there's funny
stuff but I don't add in like I
unfollowed on Instagram even like all
like the like self-deprecating and like
the gnarly ones and like the gross ones
I just like I don't really want to like
put those in my head but I see how so on
read it I just like followed I just
consume
things that interest me and like things
that I'm like if I float off dreaming
about that that ain't so bad you know
but also not stuff that's too
complicated cuz sometimes I'll be like
[__] thinking I need to like solve
all life's riddles right before bed and
I can't sleep I use Pinterest
what'swhat's your Pinterest right now
like if you go to your profile what's
like yours so I have always just done
the explore page so it's it's everything
that's like relative to my clicks or my
like my boards and my boards are very
like me they're very like my home my
relationship my friends this is what I
would like I have like baking and gifts
and just like stuff that I'm like ah
this all interests me and it all is
something that pertains to my life so it
for me Pinterest is like my own that's
very good that's very healthy yeah it is
very healthy and it's it's like oh I
have a cute closet on Pinterest but I'm
also not like I have to have this piece
because I have it in my Pinterest
because cuz Pinterest could get
unhealthy I feel like in that way like
oh I need that like all these things
that you really need but well in also I
think Pinterest I have a like
aesthetically pleasing boards for me and
I've done that as like an OCD thing but
I also know that if I like a pin and I'm
like BAM that's gonna look ugly I'll
just put it in there anyways cuz I want
to freaking know that like I want to
know you use baking soda on
such-and-such
I want to know that so that later when
I'm like how the hell do you get blood
out of your carpet like I don't know you
know okay
to kill someone because Tyler's trying
to be chip Gaines lately and he's just
bleeding everywhere we have blood on the
wall on the Pyrenees and a yes Tyler
today he was like trying to put
something up and he's just bleeding I'm
like honey here there's blood on me the
other day to go he's like you want to
take down a shed I'm like I would I want
nothing more like I would love to just
destroy a shed with you but I had to do
something else but it's just exciting to
just to go or closet wall and he was
like honey come here you have something
that you're like mad about really kick
through this wall how'd it feel did you
kick through it yeah but I got stuck so
good yeah I was bleeding we had to go
the hospital it wasn't as exciting for
me because I don't get like excitement
from like beating things up you know
he was like loving it like our house he
just has been like take that Dale take
that down fix this like Tyler I've
become like more in love with Tyler for
who he has set all of a sudden because
he just has become this like man I never
knew I never knew this side of Tyler
yeah until now it's really cool he's
like just seeing him evolve into like a
it gives him more of like a dad aspect
you know sometimes more sexy yeah you
know like he just suddenly is like I can
take a wall down like it's personal
cheerleader he's probably just like
mm-hmm take that wall do yeah anyway
that's something okay before we started
we wanted to talk about life changes and
I feel like now it's the perfect time
for you guys to talk about this let's
talk about it
Mackenzie what her life changes I feel
like I'm really evolving and growing as
a person
especially through this last year I feel
like it started I went through something
traumatic a couple years ago and I kind
of lost myself for a while but through
that I learned a lot and this past year
I made a lot of mistakes 2019 I felt
like I coped with things wrong I would
turn to not like I wanted to drink I
wanted to be distracted so I felt like
every week I was dealing with something
and every weekend I was like okay I'm
gonna go I'm gonna make plans with these
friends and these friends but everyone
knows most social things are drinking
like not all of them but most the time
lubricant you're like oh let's meet up
at this bar let's go to dinner and have
drinks or let's do this I feel I
definitely did say at some point to
Tyler like damn Mack T is partying like
crazy right yeah last year I just I I
got over relationship the year before
and I had built my life around this
person and so I didn't never knew what
it was like to be alone to be single and
I think being single kind of scared me a
little bit and like we talked about
emotions before I
want to face it like I just handled
everything in the wrong way and I was
just yeah I didn't want to sit at home
and face what was going on and learn
more about myself I was like nope I need
to be distracted you know I was just
coping totally in the wrong way
and I made a lot of mistakes and I
remember I went back to school last
October when I started going back to
school I was drinking less and I was
just more focused on my homework and
stuff and I was like looking at this
past year and I was like man I totally
did everything wrong but I don't regret
it because I learned so much through it
but last October is really when I
started taking a look at myself as a
person and who I want to be I was like I
don't want to be this person that just
pushes my feelings away and I'm going
through something and so I just need to
stay distracted
last year it was I was I needed to be
alone last year really is what it came
down to I really just needed to focus on
me and I started doing that in October
and I've become a lot happier of course
I like still go out and drink sometimes
but that was like my whole life was
involving drinking and everything and I
started writing more I started reading
more books and like taking breaks off of
social media and just doing things that
made me happy and just really realizing
my actions and what I was doing and
things like even when I was drunk you
know you say something when you're drunk
anyway I was waking up I'm like that's
not who I am like why would I even say
that like I don't want to be that person
or getting caught up in gossip I was
like this isn't the person that I want
to be but when people around drinking
and something gets brought up like
everyone kind of like goes in on it and
I was just like if I was a guy would I
want to date this person that I've been
acting like kind of like like how were
other people viewing me so I really took
a step outside of myself and I feel like
that was the best thing for me yes I
regret things but also if I wouldn't
have gone through things last year I
would probably be that same person in a
way and it's really given me a big
wake-up call like so I've just been
learning a lot
this posture and
and I like where it's headed but it
definitely takes like a lot of trial and
error and a lot of different things like
that to become that person so it's so
crazy like like it's so profound to
realize like oh like I have to go
through these things or I wouldn't learn
I wouldn't know what I know now yeah
it's like like all the strength I have
is four things that I've done and things
that have happened to me like it sucks
but like a lot of times you gotta like
once you can realize that you're through
it you can realize like oh that was just
a learning experience now I have tools
in my tool belt to go forward in my life
you know like yeah looking at last year
I was like oh I regret this re-grant
talking to this person er but then I
might know because every mistake that I
made has brought me to this point and I
know I'm not gonna do it again this
falling year I was like 2020 is my year
but then like all this bad [__] honestly
are like hell yeah 2020 is here like
which we do every year but like that
even and it's I keep saying using this
word today but aesthetically pleasing
looking at 2020 yes you like my vision
yeah yeah it's just nice it just feels
nice in it yeah okay what about you two
sharing those Mackenzie that's great
okay let's hear from you yeah oh what's
it ask me the question again changing
changes how are you feeling about like
life changes what kind of life changes
are you making um so I mean lots of
changes I feel like on so many different
like change levels I feel like I like
change more every day I adapt into
something new every day I'm just like
leaning into leaning into my healing in
every way like I've gone to the
counselor twice I was like I felt pretty
good about it like I haven't made
excuses to like stop myself from going
I've been I know I I feel like a lot of
my changes are I'm in like the trusting
my changes stage right now because I
feel like I made like so many changes
like two years ago when I just sort of
like healing and doing better but now
I'm just I'm trusting riding out those
those changes like I'm trusting that
like I can I can build
a bigger life than I thought I deserved
before you know like I can I don't know
I there's a lot of growth there's a lot
of like just changes of being it being
this age and just like kind of like
stepping into my like gifts so to say
for me honestly I huge thing for me is
is spirituality like I couldn't change
when it comes to changes like that's
it's something that I like find myself
reluctant about or I I feel like I want
like make fun of it a little bit but
like truthfully it makes me feel
fantastic I'm like learning about
spirituality and what it means to me and
like honestly like leaning into my
connection with nature like that that's
a huge change like I I really do feel
like like when I go out in the woods and
I like go for a run and I'm just
surrounded by trees like I can't even
explain it but I feel so much better and
like a lot of the changes for that is me
like admitting it out loud like I've
always would enjoy it but like I always
like would make fun of people or
something like an you know like it feels
like oh well that's not me that's not my
identity and so I had to like negated or
something so I guess leaning into my
changes to accepting my changes and like
allowing them to like carry me forward I
suppose yeah I guess nothing
specifically I guess but I think nature
so great it really is you know I just
watched a Paul Stamets it's a fantastic
fungi he just released it it's it's now
out but Megan and I it like two weeks
ago I went and saw it in Portland out a
theatre and it's so good and it's just
like about mushrooms and nature I don't
want to go on about it but seriously
anybody listening watch that fantastic
fungi Jessica what a changes like I feel
like we should probably tell and I
should probably watch that he's all in
oh my god
yes coming again coming again love you
babe your you're hot you're hot Tyler I
had any smart hi Tyler
hmm well I think we like kind of touch
base on a few of the things that like
changes in my life like overall things
have been just shifting a little bit but
I think my mindset has been changing a
lot too like this is so silly but I did
this yesterday and maybe it's the Co
virus or maybe it's just me she has the
virus I so because we're starting this
business we like obviously have to
decide when your branding something in a
business you have to say like I choose
to have these core values that's a just
that's like a very basic business
mindset however at the end of the day
like people want to know or like to be
like business I guess maybe just this
generic structured business we need to
have these core values and like I have
integrity and I say that and I say it
with almost this like I'm doing an
injustice to the word integrity because
this whole time I thought I have
integrity because I say I'm gonna do
what I do sometimes I don't like my
friends are like you coming over yeah
for sure and then it gets to that day
and I'm like little cancelling mmm
because I know for my own well-being I
need to cancel I need to take that break
I need that moment but like I went to
the bathroom yesterday and I was like
being extra cautious with my paper towel
so I never opened the door with a paper
towel because I don't give a [__] like I
I'm gonna have germs and that's just how
it's gonna be and whatever and I've
always been very like I don't care about
germs but like I used that because I'm
being extra cautious I use the paper
towel and then I like threw it the trash
and it didn't make him in the trash and
I walked out the door and like I
literally door Dyneema shut and I like
ran back into the door as it's closing
on me and I was like damn it has some
damn integrity like I had a self talk
where I was like go pick that [__] up
off the floor cuz I know I get mad when
I go to a restroom and there's paper
towels all over the farm like well y'all
are dicks and I think about it from like
a woman's standpoint like women are
pissed when their husband doesn't pick
up their socks off the floor but they're
gonna throw their trash on the floor and
then I think like well I'm not having
any integrity if I don't like walk back
and do that so I would say like as of
lately like very recently integrity has
been huge on my mind it's just been
something because I do feel like i tend
to say like like and i've done this to
you a lot yeah I'm for sure down today
this day and then the day gets here and
I'm like not for it which I know you
understand my like oh yeah sorry
canceling cuz I just need a brain break
or I need a mint you know I need I need
an emotional something but I don't feel
like everyone understands that and I
hate when I say I'll do something and I
don't do it and my my friends Jessie and
Lacey we were talking about like words
that describe you know Lacey and I and
they they had said reliable and I like
questioned it like to it like am i
reliable yeah I literally was you guys
think I'm reliable huh and like I know
I'm reliable I know I am but I also know
that I waver a lot of times where I'm
not but when I say I will be at
something and it is a for sure I'm gonna
be there I will show up and I will be
there 100% but I know there are times
where I'm like yeah I'll come but I
don't actually mean it like I know I'm
so questioning if I want to be there
like so like what someone catches you
off-guard they're like I'll be so caught
up with the momentum of the exciting
conversation I'm like bro I'm coming
I'll say I bought a ticket already like
sometimes you get excited in the moment
there's that also I think it's important
like you were saying for your self-care
like if you really if you're in a state
and you're like I don't need to be
around people in it or I need to I
haven't had a moment to myself and I'm
not gonna be fully present in this
moment I need some time to myself before
I meet up with someone I think it's good
to recognize that because you got to
think about yourself sometimes you know
I think that's the thing maybe I've
always done probably and I just don't
I'm just now reflecting on it enough to
say like guys for a long time I've been
the person who's like yeah I can for
sure do that I would love to be there
and I'm a yes person I always want to be
there I always want to go do stuff like
I absolutely want to be involved but I
know that I give a lot of myself away
mm-hmm a lot of the time and I know that
there are times where I just need to I
need to look and I say this like you
guys probably think I'm joking but like
I will I want to lay on my couch and
stare at the ceiling well and for me
that sounds right moment of just like
nothing and I want to have that because
I'm constant like I was saying I'm
constantly like you're there that you
know I'm just being able to like let
your mind unwind just taking some time
to yourself it sometimes it feels great
not to think about any
just nothing like I don't don't solve
anything right now yeah like don't even
I just wanted to be in my room
I want to either just stare at the
ceiling or maybe I want to watch one
tree hit like mindless drama I put on
Parks and Rec for the millionth time
right watch it you know but I don't like
you just kind of like huh huh everyone
friends used to be on TV cuz me too I've
been like really watching well the
office I like fall asleep to it every
night even though I've seen it a million
times it's just that thing that's there
and then I can just like unwind in my
room turn off the other stuff and just
feel comfortable yeah yeah I like that
Jessica I think just like it's funny
that you were like immediately hard of
yourself like oh like I'm really you
guys think I'm reliable because like
reliable could mean something different
you know in that context you're like oh
I can't all the time they're like like
we do too like they probably haven't
think about things were like no in these
ways you're reliable yeah that's what
they're thinking I I have a like the
first I don't know I feel like I was
like more flaky at the beginning of the
podcast like I feel like if the other
person wasn't like 100% like all in I'm
that cool it's fine man no big deal like
don't don't come but now I have like
something I feel like I'm building a
little integrity there to like I'm I'm
trying to like if I schedule a podcast
like I'm gonna make it happen
yeah and for me sometimes making it
happen in this like crazy world means
that like I text them three days before
and then I catch them the day before
like hey he's still good for my like
yeah I feel like I actually had a day
where I drank the night before like I
ended up having just a fun night like
randomly like friends came over and then
we met up with that we saw Jack dark and
I came over to the top house and it was
just like it was just one of those
nights for me yeah and you know like I
really I don't have any work to do and
we got drunk I had just just the
greatest time I felt [__] terrible
next morning woke up and I had a podcast
at 11:00 and a the first initial thing I
was like I should text him and see if I
can get a couple hours later or you know
whatever I can try like swindle my way
out of it but right right away I was
like no man you drank
you're gonna do that podcast hungover if
that's what it is like and you're gonna
show out like you're going to you made
the right notes yeah you're going to or
like if you are feeling too shitty like
you're going to go outside and you're
workout tell you Peter can get that out
and feel better like that's my mindset
now with with that but it's cool like a
it's like a passion though for you then
yeah like like assigning yourself to
that but I don't know I feel like you're
the same way like like you're building
this this bartending business and it's
like the same thing you're like who do I
want to what side of me do I want to
represent what like how do I want to
hold myself accountable yeah and these
ways you know and I feel like you kind
of got to make your own rules and give
them power you know I think that's
pretty powerful Lucy Knight because we
always hang out we always hang out we're
like hey what are you doing today
we don't work to for a cool let's hang
out for three hours or whatever but we
had we legitimately on Thursday we're
like it is a business meeting we cannot
cancel it we cannot change it we are
having a bit because otherwise Lacey and
I are just gonna chill and probably make
lunch the funnest I'm like whatever we
feel like doing like let's let's walk
the dog but we had to like yeah we're
doing this that that's something really
cool I think how about that so like
entrepreneurs or people who are like
trying to do something passionate or
something serious like making rules for
your hangouts like because I feel like
Brandon and I do it like we where we
flirt with it we haven't successfully
totally don't say yeah like well I mean
we'll make beats and stuff we'll do like
super fun stuff but like we have had
times with brillig let's meet up and
let's just get a video done today or
let's just get a song or you know
whatever it is I think more people
should like go into their friend groups
like if you have creator friend group so
you have like entrepreneur friend groups
or even just one homie like hey man I do
want to hang out today but like let's
just make sure we get this thing done
but yeah more let's make sure we like
just focus on this and if something fun
comes up and of course like we make a
man all of garden sounds good let's go
to Olive Garden like of course it's
gonna sound good [__] all good I
think I think it is cool to see you know
as much as I I try to kind of push like
your friends or your counselors your
friends your therapist your friends your
family your friends are like you can
talk to them about things you don't have
to schedule this thing and be otherwise
like if your passion is if you love your
friends but your passion is like your
business and they have another business
that coincides you guys can work
together like say hey man like we're
gonna hang out a Wednesday but like but
hangout let's let's do six [__] hours
of business work yeah didn't hang yeah
yes that's not always just like don't
talk to me and I'm just going to write
this like microsoft word document you
know but well it's hard cuz being
friends to you're like oh guess what
happened yesterday are you like you know
you get to form a discipline though it
is no way it was and it is something
that like Lacey and I are very much like
we are you just want to chill hey could
we wanted let's paint today let's go for
a walk let's go for a hike
let's go whatever and we have to be very
but I also find that with even with
Tyler like I have to say like babe we
gotta like sit down and get serious
about this because he's he's learning to
code right now and like I want him to
succeed in that I want to hang out with
him and like I just want to sit with him
on the couch and watch some dumb movie
and just be near his presence but I also
Mike I should not talk honey you need to
go do your thing like you need to go do
your school and like we'll set will set
time limits where he's like can't I have
these two classes probably like another
hour okay then in an hour like I'll try
not to bother him you know like I'm like
the dog where I like walk in the room
like okay verify you know it's 4:13 okay
but I think that like even with us we'll
say like can we gotta get a podcast done
today or we gotta like get this done
today and it's I think it has to be like
that with a lot of my friends because
they are also creators like Brandon he
knows when we all come over like he
wants to chill for a minute but he'll
like like slowly just like sink away and
his into his office go get some stuff
done and I'm like that's perfect I'm
glad you feel comfortable doing that
yeah because it is like you know I'm
trying to be your friend but I'm also
trying to run a business and have a
passion and like yeah he's lonely like
see ya so I think it's I think for our
for our friends specifically because
we're all just kind of like creating and
growing and whatever even if we're not
all entrepreneurs right we all have to
take that time to like get our [__] done
and hang out because you can do it yeah
he's got to have boundaries yeah you
gotta have boundaries you know I like
try to balance it like how it like we
can we can do that thing we could play
Super Smash Bros with like let's get
done first yeah give yourself a little
bit of cookies all the beers all the way
up until then and then like when we're
ready
dude that's another thing like trying to
be productive like like there's so much
like weed and alcohol in my world like
it's just always I go to the Portland
studio and they'll like like the
engineers like that they'll be smoking
all day and they're they're totally fine
with doing it and they're like the
people come in like rappers come in and
they're they're smoking and they're more
comfortable when there's a couple of
drinks and they got a couple of friends
it's so weird like it has still work
though like it's fun like that whole
situation could turn into just drinking
and hanging it out yeah but you got to
be like hey I'm in that vibe now let me
pull myself out of that vibe to have a
like a plan beforehand remember how you
were I think we've talked about this
like I have to set my art studio up
before I can go paint if I think I'm
gonna smoke or drink I have to have
things like prepared for me to work or
my brain my mindset has to be I'm doing
this to assist me in my creativity or
assist me in my productivity like I've
gotten that down pretty well down here I
pretty much have it set up like to where
it's it's ready to go like whatever like
I can be intuitive and I can like oh I
feel like doing that creative thing
right now I can do it but like you do
got to prep like ahead of time like make
sure it's all laid out I want to get
better at like I want to get a bunch of
like creators down here and much
musicians and stuff and I want to be
like the the guy who's like it gets us
working yeah we need like stations yeah
yeah I mean I do I need that compartment
like give me this workstation and you
can be here in your little space and
then like you can still chat with
everyone but like hear me you can still
chat with I gotta make little cubby
holes though I guess cut up your folders
it's hard being it's hard I don't know
creating something without somebody
else's rules is difficult like you you
know in the
being a creator you don't you don't go
and say be here Monday at 8 a.m. unless
you say be here at Monday 8 a.m.
like you don't get this particular thing
done until you say it you know you got
to like create your own and I think
learning that power like it's great for
entrepreneur but it's good for everybody
like it's great for like it's like a
powerful skill that I slowly feel I
guess it's another change is like
sharpening yeah getting there yeah that
is a big change actually yeah telling
yourself you have to do it yeah like
like me well don't work yeah oh boy so
change is [__] fantastic change is
great I feel like allowing yourself room
for change and allowing other people to
change and allowing I think like just
really letting yourself see yourself as
like you know like with this podcast for
example I'm like if there's any time
where I think I'm sounding cool and I'm
changed like all these things but like
in 3 years I might listen to this exact
same wording like I was an idiot I
changed a lot yeah this is impermanence
man that's what this is all about life
is always changing and I think if you
just just kind of like point your sails
that you know you know growth just like
believing in yourself you know as corny
as it sounds but like just knowing like
I'm doing this thing right now and and
I'm going towards improvement though so
even if it's not working out for me I
know that it's going to I've been
listening to the EM Rachel Hollis
podcast so good is it the D whatever yes
the rise podcast yeah
it's so good she's so just I'm like
amped every time I listen to it but she
said something that was pretty profound
for me that was like her one of her
podcasts I think the name was like
you're not prepared for who you're gonna
be in two years and she like sat on the
stage with like her CFO her husband cuz
her and her husband are like the CEOs of
the company her like creative her social
media like all these all these like
bosses essentially in her company and
she basically said like every person on
this stage is not prepared for what
they're who they're gonna be in two
years or what they're gonna need to know
or their skills but we're like
constantly learning and every time we
make a mistake we learn from it and it
was like that was a good feeling
like something to hear because I'm
always thinking like man I really wish I
knew this like the Excel thing I wish I
knew more about Excel okay well in in a
month I could know the hell of a lot
more about Excel if I just put my mind
to it and I know that that's part of
what I need to learn you know I know
that was a profound little like dude I
mean that that's everything instead of
saying like I don't know this it's
literally all you have to do is say like
I have the capability of knowing that
yes and then when you just like believe
believe that and you just put in the
work you'll be surprised but oh yeah if
I like you know I don't think you ever
get two points I feel like we learn a
lot of excels like we learn a lot of
those things without us realizing like
what lecture I don't know this but we
don't really stop to be like that's how
we are dude like you just have to like
think I don't know how to do that but I
can bet I can do it or yeah I don't know
how to how to handle that thing that's
coming up but like I trust that when
that time comes I'm gonna be prepared
I'm gonna know or and if I'm not I'm not
gonna die yeah I'm gonna figure that out
too well Crona no no I think with me
I've just been every day I want to grow
like that's been my mindset has just
been I don't want to take steps back
like whatever I do even if it's making a
mistake
okay I'm growing from that like I'm not
gonna go backwards and I think that's a
way to like just look at life right now
it's just wanting to be a better person
than I was the day before I do just
think about that like like in five years
if you do that every day you know like
it's inevitable that you're gonna be
like oh I'm I'm in more advanced than I
was five years ago yeah like it's it's
what you're making the choice yeah you
just got to make that choice that's like
I'm going to I'm gonna I'm gonna lean
towards growth a growth mindset that's
what I'm gonna do
it's all about how we handle situation
it's literally us like we make our
decisions yes things happen to us but
it's how we handle it and grow from it
like you can choose like last year I
could choose to drink every weekend and
I'm going nowhere or this year I'm like
wow I'm realizing so much about myself
because I'm sober
when you were doing all that like you
were making a lot of memories with a lot
of people yeah it was sometimes like
you're like I just drank a lot but like
I have a lot of memories with a lot of
people and like I grew a lot of
friendships through that and then I also
had to be sober and then realize are
these my friends or these my party
friends yeah my pants up and I have to
pee
a couple more minutes no it was a super
fun year like like I said I don't regret
anything I do have a lot of great
memories but yeah like looking at myself
like I should have been being okay with
being single and being alone and instead
I was like I need to be around people I
can't be my by myself and I'm that says
you should have been though who is it
the tells you you should have been cuz
you have like you like I noticed you
saying like I made the wrong choices but
like who decides that those are the
wrong choices or were they just things
that you did and in the moment that was
the best you knew what to do with what
you the knowledge you had yeah and then
you realized cuz you learn and you
decided to grow yeah I feel like when it
comes to you know not not every
situation is the same when it comes to
like vices I feel like I just like I'm
so sympathetic I word but I just like I
get it like sometimes we're just going
through some [__] like sometimes you're
just I'm in that stage of them just
smoking a lot of [__] weed right now
where I'm I'm you know I'm drinking more
than I want to right now I think I'm
kind of dealing with some [__] like I
feel like even those sentences like
those things like nobody's around you is
like like okay like I understand that
cuz I get the same things you know said
we see everybody is a call yeah you're
an addict or you have this thing or like
oh you're drinking a lot or all these
things but it's [__] we all have that
man like it's like the homeless guys
like you know a lot of times maybe they
have like their shoot needles into their
arms and their vices a lot worse than
ours
yeah do we all just humans have the
capability of not only being like
addicted to things but of of using like
a way of living
as you know avoidance but also enjoying
life because it's not like we're like
I'm trying to make myself miserable like
you're enjoying your life yeah I
definitely have fun yeah about the the
value of like the the glass tabletop
outside there was like a little bit of
green algae on the sides and it's a
glass table we've all been on a deck
having those late-night conversations
drunk with friends before at a glass
table like that's valuable yeah yeah
those conversations built your
relationship right those times that
we've had a lot of drunk conversation
it's fine dude everybody it's it's it's
not it's okay just know that like it
when you want to like if it's something
that you want to step into or you want
to be a growth mindset person yeah the
cool part is like all of us who have
like party together are also growing
together yes you know so like there
there is I mean there are obviously a
few who have like kind of straight off
or there they started having kids long
before we did so we're not sure about
that type of but we're still like there
there's still a pretty big group of us
mm-hmm and I feel like a lot of my
friends are in the same mindset as I am
or the same realm like I think I'm in my
time of life where like y'all are in the
same I don't feel like I'm like my
friend I can't like coach my friends and
be like oh my god you guys I learned
this cool thing today like it's it's too
much for somebody to grasp the friends
that I can't say that to I'm not even
friends with anymore I don't talk to you
yeah you know I got to feel like anytime
I can be like Jake guess what happened
today this cool thing happened matter
guess what you know like I know
absolutely I love getting texts like
that yeah what do you know somebody's
gonna be supportive like in this genuine
like they're like dude like if you told
me like guess what happened today and
it's something that just happened with
you has nothing to do with my life like
it would generally bring me joy to our
life over here you're like hey this good
thing happened to me and I love you guys
my friends so like of course I'm gonna
be feeling good for you yeah right yeah
it's cool to have that I think we get
used to a lot of like you know not just
like mean or like self-deprecating but
like a lot of like dude you're not super
encouraging to me are you or you know
or just like making fun of people or
like friendships that don't really like
fill you with much yeah yeah it's
encouragement I had yesterday or two
days ago I walked out of the house and
I'm just like a reminder of like my
family of like the being made fun of
thing like I had someone I haven't seen
him in years he's like a cousin's friend
or maybe like one of my distant cousins
picking up my mom's car essentially I
walked out the house and I was wearing
like a brimmed hat and he just goes what
the [__] and like those sort of things
it was just this quick like example of
like oh yeah that's like why I don't
choose to even surround myself with
these sort of people yeah you know the
fact that it's like family is relevant
like I'm not just super close to my
family so that's an easy avoidance for
me yeah but it's things like that a
reminder like I wasn't upset it was more
just like oh you know like I don't hang
out people like I haven't heard anybody
insult me like that for a while I had to
explain my outfit to everyone I'm
hanging out with every day for a while
oh yeah like I'm just being myself and
my friends except me you know like
normally I walk if I walk out and it was
five of my friends standing out there
they'd be like oh like they would
probably talk to me and not notice my
outfit because that's just I'm just
wearing it's a [__] piece of clothing
on me whatever yeah or they would
compliment me if they really did like it
or whatever and I think that outside of
like physical appearance stuff I think
when we say things like when we are when
we're dreamers out loud or when we're
like I'm talking about real things we
have people who aren't supportive
sometimes you know I think just being
being encouraging to your friends it's
good and choosing friends that are
encouraging to you yeah I've definitely
the past couple years had to choose do I
want to really continue like I really
was putting effort yeah like before I
didn't really think about it and then
when you go through traumatic stuff or
like you're trying to focus on yourself
and it's not just a party front you know
what I mean you're like oh I really want
this person in my life like they bring
benefits to my life they bring joy
they're positive I've really had to
decide on certain friends throughout the
past years like they're not nice
something like this I could say a lot of
mean things I'm just gonna say they're
not nice or you know so I think I have a
lot of friends who were just service
trends you know who I'm like I I value
you as a person but I don't think we
have a lot in common anymore or I don't
think that we have a lot to talk about
or whatever and like I still hold you to
the highest with the utmost respect like
I I just don't we don't see the same or
have the same lifestyle or understand
the same things yeah and like I still
respect you as a person and I would love
to like sure I'll grab coffee with you
and I don't mind but like I'm not going
to go out of my way to put forth effort
to keeping this relationship going if
it's not gonna benefit not not like in a
selfish way but like I need my lifestyle
and my the people in my life to be
supportive and strong and and equal I
need someone to level up yeah my friends
to level up to where I'm at yeah you can
literally say I don't make it I don't I
don't hang out with people who make fun
of me yeah or I don't hang out with
people who are encouraging yeah you can
say that you can pick your friends it is
straining when you're hanging out with
someone and you're trying to have this
vibe and be positive and talk about
important things or just having like
real deep conversations if I'm sitting
there someone and they they don't want a
hat like talk about something it's all
superficial like they don't want to talk
about real stuff I'm like well this is
Who I am like I want to talk about good
let's dive in deep like I want to know
who you are I don't genuinely care about
like your life but they're like nope
like I don't know it just depends and I
guess some people are closed off but if
it's a continuous things like over the
years and you can't get to know who your
friends are and they don't want to share
and they're negative around you it's
kind of like okay same thing like oh
we're still friends but I kind of just
like need people in my life thought
that's a that's self-love right there
honestly just you know it's they are who
they are and you can't control that
that's yeah like it's you don't hate
their guts and hope they die yeah it's
just like I'm choosing to follow like
what's true to me is is to surround
myself with people who influence me and
unfortunately like you don't seem to be
doing that you know and I think that's
okay yeah that's looking out for
yourself I think it's hard for people
some people to hear but I also think
it's so important for people to hear and
the other thing is like I I know that
like I've seen the ugliest and the worst
of my friends and
you know their reciprocal like I have
also shown them the ugliest and the
worst of me and they're still here and
there are friends who like when they see
the uglier parts you can feel them slack
off right and you know they they might
have friends who they are willing to
show their ugliest to but it's not me
or you know I think everyone probably
has that but I definitely feel myself
being more like drawn to spending time
with people who I feel like I can go
wake up and roll out of bed and look
like [__] and feel like [__] and talk
weird and say dumb things and they're
just like we're still friends yeah you
know like I support you you're cool
right like you're your brimmed hat you
know like I probably be like hey what
about it also though that guy would have
said something like whoa not a fan of
your hat you know like I don't love that
or something along the lines that
personally brought it to him and his
decision on it versus you wearing it
like he instead of him saying what that
back we could have been like hey nice
hat bro not a huge fan but like you seem
like to like you like it then you'd be
like foot and move on like yellow yeah
what he really meant was that hat is not
something that I would wear right that's
what he meant to say but instead he said
what the [__] and it's just so like what
but it was funny because I used to like
how something like that would get me
self-conscious about like fact it is
this attitude like I don't want to deal
with that or I'd be like I don't want to
deal with thinking everyone is in their
mind or to their significant they're
saying what the [__] and when I go to
Walmart or whatever it is yeah but it's
my stomach growled so you guys just okay
hey let's end it out anyway because I
want to grab another beer and we'll get
some food so Mackenzie and Jessica I
appreciate you both thanks for coming
over and talking about whatever we can
do it fairly often yeah we'll get uh
we'll get it poppin with us again - yeah
exciting yeah I plant this thing's gonna
keep going for a while so give the
message give the listeners a message
love yourself
love yourself don't drink and drive
actually use hand sanitizer oh yeah
don't spread Cronin yeah that's a
message talk to yourself wash your hands
love yourself and use hand sanitizer and
white give you our teas and what but in
sod I know the toilet paper yeah like we
need some two day upstairs can I steal a
roll I'm getting this bidet go it's
funny cuz its way cleaner than toilet
paper like we just dry wipe our butt
okay that's good
imagine if you had poop on your hands
and you just wipe it off with a dry you
be like that's good let's go room a day
like we're so gross what the [__] is
going on anyway use a bidet wash your
hands love yourself see you later
junkyard lovers hi bye
you